<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
 SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2018 Volker Krause <vkrause@kde.org>
 SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.itinerary</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <developer id="kde.org">
    <name translate="no">KDE</name>
  </developer>
  <name>KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">مُخطِط الرحلة لكيدي</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Itinerář KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KDE-Itinero</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KDE itineraar</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">केडीई यात्रा कार्यक्रम</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Adde a KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDE 여행 정보</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Маршруты KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sa">केडीई यात्रासूची</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDE Itinerár</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KDE Yol Kılavuzu</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE 旅行計劃</name>
  <summary>Digital travel assistant</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">مُخطِط الرحلة مساعد سفر رقمي</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Assistent digital de viatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Assistent digital de viatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Digitální asistent na cesty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Digitaler Reiseassistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Digital travel assistant</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Cifereca vojaĝasistanto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Asistente digital para viajes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Digitaalne reisimise abivahend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Bidai-laguntzaile digitala</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Ohjelmallinen matka-avustaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Assistance de voyage numérique</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Asistente de viaxes dixital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">מסייע דיגיטלי לנסיעות</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hi">डिजिटल यात्रा सहायक</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Digitális utazássegéd</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Assistente digital de viage</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Asisten travel digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Assistente digitale per i viaggi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">მოგზაურობის ციფრული დამხმარე</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">디지털 여행 도우미</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Digitale reisassistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Cyfrowy pomocnik podróży</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Assistente de viagens digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Assistente de viagens digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Цифровой помощник в путешествиях</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sa">डिजिटल यात्रा सहायक</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Digitálny cestovný asistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Digitalni potovalni pomočnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Digitalt resehjälpprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sayısal yolculuk asistanı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Цифровий помічник у подорожах</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">数字旅行助理应用</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">數位旅行助理</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Itinerary is a digital travel assistant with a priority on protecting your privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">مخطط رحلة كيدي هو مساعد سفر رقمي يولي الأولوية لحماية خصوصيتك.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Itinerary és un assistent digital de viatges amb la prioritat de protegir la vostra privadesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Itinerary és un assistent digital de viatges amb la prioritat de protegir la vostra privadesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Itinerář KDE je digitální asistent na cestování jehož prioritou je ochrana vašeho soukromí.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KDE-Itinerary ist ein digitaler Reiseassistent, der den Schutz Ihrer Privatsphäre priorisiert.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Itinerary is a digital travel assistant with a priority on protecting your privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KDE-Itinero estas cifereca vojaĝasistanto kun prioritato pri protektado de via privateco.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary es un asistente de viajes digital que tiene como prioridad proteger su privacidad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KDE Itineraar on digitaalne reisiabiline, mis seab sihiks sinu privaatsuse kaitsmise.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«KDE Itinerary» bidai-laguntzaile digital bat da, zure pribatutasuna babesteko lehentasuna duena.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KDE Itinerary on ohjelmallinen matka-avustaja, joka ensisijaisesti pyrkii varmistamaan tietoturvasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDE Itinerary est un assistant de voyage numérique donnant la priorité au respect de votre confidentialité.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KDE Itinerary é un asistente dixital de viaxe coa protección da súa privacidade como prioridade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KDE Itinerary הוא מסייע דיגיטלי לנסיעות שמקדש את השמירה על הפרטיות שלך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">केडीई इटीनरेरी एक डिजिटल यात्रा सहायक है जिसकी प्राथमिकता आपकी गोपनीयता की सुरक्षा है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KDE Itinerary egy digitális utazássegéd, amelynek kiemelt célja a magánszférájának védelme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KDE Itinerary es un assistente digital de viage con le prioritate de proteger tu confidentialitate.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KDE Itinerary adalah asisten perjalanan digital dengan prioritas melindungi privasimu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary è un assistente di viaggio digitale con una priorità sulla protezionedella tua riservatezza.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KDE Itinerary მოგზაურობის ციფრული დამხმარეა, თქვენი კონფიდენციალობის შენარჩუნების პრიორიტეტით.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDE 여행 정보는 프라이버시를 지키는 디지털 여행 도우미입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary is een digitale reisassistent met prioriteit op beschermen van uw privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KDE Itinerary jest cyfrowym pomocnikiem podróży, którego nadrzędnym celem jest chronienie twojej prywatności.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Itinerary é um assistente digital de viagens com a prioridade de proteger a sua privacidade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDE Itinerary é um assistente de viagens digital com prioridade na proteção de sua privacidade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Маршруты KDE — это цифровой помощник в путешествиях, в котором сделан акцент на обеспечении конфиденциальности пользователя.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">KDE Itinerary एकः डिजिटलयात्रासहायकः अस्ति यस्य प्राथमिकता भवतः गोपनीयतायाः रक्षणं भवति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KDE Itinerary je digitalni pomočnik pri potovanju s pomembno zasnovo pri zaščiti vaše zasebnosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan är ett digitalt resehjälpprogram som prioriterar att skydda din integritet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KDE Yol Kılavuzu, gizliliğinize öncelik veren bir sayısal yolculuk asistanıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary — цифровий помічник у подорожах, акцент у якому зроблено на забезпеченні вашої конфіденційності.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Itinerary 是一款注重保护用户隐私的数字旅行助理应用。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">《KDE 旅行計劃》是一個重視保護您的隱私權的數位旅行助理。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">الميزات:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Trajtoj:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Eginbideak:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">יכולות:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">विशेषताएँ:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Funkciók:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">თვისებები:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">गुणाः:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Timeline view of a unified travel itinerary with automatic trip grouping.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عرض زمني لمخطط رحلة موحّد مع تجميع تلقائي للرحلات.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Visualització de la línia de temps d'un itinerari unificat de viatges amb agrupació automàtica de viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Visualització de la línia de temps d'un itinerari unificat de viatges amb agrupació automàtica de viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Zeitleistenansicht eines vereinten Reiseplans mit automatischer Reisegruppierung.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Timeline view of a unified travel itinerary with automatic trip grouping.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Templiniovido de unuigita vojaĝa itinero kun aŭtomata vojaĝgrupo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista cronológica de un itinerario de viaje unificado con agrupación de viajes automática.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ühendatud reisikava ajateljevaade ühes võimalusega reise automaatselt rühmitada.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bidai ibilbide bateratu baten denbora-lerro ikuspegia, txango taldekatze automatikoarekin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Yhtenäisen matkasuunnitelman aikajananäkymä matkan automaattisella ryhmittelyllä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Vue chronologique de votre itinéraire de voyage unifié grâce au regroupement automatique des voyages.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Vista da cronoloxía dun itinerario de viaxe sen definir con agrupamento automático de viaxes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תצוגת ציר זמן של תוכנית נסיעה אחודה עם קיבוץ נסיעות אוטומטי.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">स्वचालित यात्रा समूहीकरण के साथ एकीकृत यात्रा कार्यक्रम का समयरेखा दृश्य।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Idővonal nézet az egyesített útvonaltervhez, automatikus kiránduláscsoportosítással.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Vista de chronologia de unitinerario unificate viage con gruppamento de viages automatic.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tampilan garis waktu dari rencana perjalanan terpadu dengan pengelompokan perjalanan otomatis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione della sequenza temporale di un itinerario di viaggio unificato con raggruppamento automatico dei viaggi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">Itinerrary-ის გაერთიანებული მოგზაურობის ხედი დროის ხაზზე, მოვლენების ავტომატური დაჯგუფებით.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">자동 여행 그룹 기능이 있는 통합된 여정 타임라인 보기.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Tijdlijn weergave van een geünificeerd reisroute met automatische groepering van trips.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Widok osi czasu dla ujednoliconego planu podróży z samoczynnym grupowaniem podróży.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Visão cronológica de um itinerário de viagens unificado com o agrupamento automático das viagens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição cronológica de um itinerário de viagem unificado com agrupamento automático de viagem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Просмотр расписания унифицированного маршрута с автоматической группировкой по поездкам.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">स्वचालितयात्रासमूहीकरणेन सह एकीकृतयात्रायात्रासूचिकायाः समयरेखादृश्यम्।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pogled časovnice poenotenega plana potovanja s samodejnim grupiranjem potovanj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">TIdslinjevisning av en enhetlig resplan med automatisk resegruppering.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Otomatik yolculuk gruplandırması ile birleşik yolcu belgelerinin zaman akışı görünümü.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу уніфікованого маршруту подорожі із автоматичним групуванням за поїздками.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">时间线视图，可自动分组并归类旅程。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">整合旅行計劃的時間軸，支援自動為旅程分組。</li>
      <li>Supports train, bus and flight bookings as well as hotel, restaurant, event and rental car reservations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم حجوزات القطارات والحافلات والرحلات الجوية، بالإضافة إلى حجوزات الفنادق والمطاعم والفعاليات والسيارات المستأجرة.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet reserves de tren, autobús i avió, així com reserves d'hotels, restaurants, esdeveniments i lloguer de cotxes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet reserves de tren, autobús i avió, així com reserves d'hotels, restaurants, esdeveniments i lloguer de cotxes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Zug-, Bus- und Flugbuchungen sowie für Hotel-, Restaurant-, Veranstaltungs- und Mietwagenreservierungen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports train, bus and flight bookings as well as hotel, restaurant, event and rental car reservations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Subtenas rezervojn de trajno, buso kaj flugo kaj ankaŭ rezervojn de hotelo, restoracio, evento kaj luaŭto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite el uso de reservas de trenes, autobuses y vuelos, así como de hoteles, restaurantes, eventos y alquiler de automóviles.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rongide, busside ja lennukite ning hotellide, restoranide, sündmuste ja rendiautode broneeringud ja reserveeringud.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Tren, autobus eta hegaldi erreserbak onartzen ditu, baita hotel, jatetxe, ekitaldi eta ibilgailu alokairuenak ere.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee juna-, bussi- ja lentolippujen samoin kuin hotellien, ravintoloiden, tapahtumien ja vuokra-autojen varauksia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge des réservations de trains, de bus, de vols, d'hôtels, de restaurants, d'évènements et de véhicules.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite billetes de tren, bus e voo, así como reservas de hotel, restaurante, eventos e alugamento de coche.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תמיכה בהזמנות של רכבות, אוטובוסים וטיסות לרבות הזמנות במלונות, מסעדות, אירועים והשכרות רכב.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">ट्रेन, बस और उड़ान बुकिंग के साथ-साथ होटल, रेस्तरां, कार्यक्रम और किराये की कार आरक्षण का समर्थन करता है।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Vonat-, busz és repülőjegyek, valamint hotel-, étterem-, eseményfoglalások és autóbérlés támogatása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Supporta reservationes de traino, bus e volo tal como hotel, restaurante, eventos e reservationes de location de vehiculo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Mendukung pemesanan kereta api, bus dan penerbangan serta pemesanan hotel, restoran, acara dan persewaan mobil.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta prenotazioni per treni, autobus e voli aerei così come alberghi, ristoranti, eventi e noleggi auto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აქვს მატარებლის, ავტობუსის და ფრენის ბილეთების დაჯავშნის, ასევე სასტუმროს, რესტორანის, მოვლენისა და მანქანის ქირაობის რეზერვაციების მხარდაჭერა.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">철도, 버스, 항공 예약 이외에도 호텔, 레스토랑, 행사, 렌터카 예약도 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt boekingen van trein, bus en vlucht evenals reserveringen van hotel, restaurant, evenement en huurauto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje bilety na pociągi, autobusy i samoloty, a także hotele, restauracje, wydarzenia i wypożyczanie samochodów.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta as reservas de comboios, autocarros e voos, assim como dos hotéis, restaurantes, eventos e alugueres de carros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporta reservas de trens, ônibus e voos, bem como reservas de hotéis, restaurantes, eventos e aluguel de veículos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка заказа билетов на поезда, автобусы и самолеты, а также бронирования прокатных автомобилей, гостиничных номеров, мест в ресторанах и посещения мероприятий.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">रेलयानस्य, बसयानस्य, विमानस्य च बुकिंगस्य समर्थनं करोति तथा च होटेल्, रेस्टोरन्ट्, इवेण्ट्, किरायेण कारस्य आरक्षणं च समर्थयति ।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira rezervacije vlakov, avtobusov in letal kot tudi hotelov, restavracij, dogodkov in rezervacij najema avtomobilov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder tåg-, buss-, och flygbokningar samt bokning av hotell, restauranger, evenemang och hyrbilar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tren, otobüs ve uçak rezervasyonlarının yanı sıra otel, restoran ve kiralık araç rezervasyonlarını da destekler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка бронювання квитків на потяги, автобуси та літаки, а також бронювання номерів готелів, місць у ресторанах, участі у подіях та оренди автомобілів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持预订火车、公共汽车、航班、酒店、餐厅、活动和租车服务。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援鐵路、公路與航空訂票，以及飯店、餐廳、活動與租車預約。</li>
      <li>Boarding pass management.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إدارة بطاقات الصعود إلى الطائرة.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Gestió de les targetes d'embarcament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestioneu les targetes d'embarcament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Bordkartenverwaltung.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Boarding pass management.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Administrado de enirpermesiloj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Gestión de tarjetas de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Piletite haldus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Ontziratze-txartelen kudeaketa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Maihinnousukorttien hallinta</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion des cartes d'embarquement.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Xestión de pases de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">ניהול כרטיסי עלייה למטוס.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">बोर्डिंग पास प्रबंधन.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Beszállókártya-kezelés.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Gestion de carta de imbarcar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pengelolaan boarding pass.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Gestione delle carte d'imbarco.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ჩასაჯდომი ბილეთების მართვა.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">탑승권 관리.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Beheer van boardingpass</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie kartami pokładowymi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gestão de cartões de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciamento de cartões de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Управление посадочными талонами.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">बोर्डिंग पास प्रबन्धन।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Správa leteniek</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Upravljanje vstopnih kuponov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hantering av boardingkort.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Biniş kartı yönetimi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Керування посадковими квитками.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">登机牌管理。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">登機證管理。</li>
      <li>Supports ticket management for multi-traveler and multi-ticket bookings.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يدعم إدارة التذاكر للحجوزات متعددة المسافرين والمتعددة التذاكر.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet la gestió de bitllets per a reserves multiviatger i multibitllet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet la gestió de bitllets per a reserves multiviatger i multibitllet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützt die Ticketverwaltung für Mehrpersonenreisen und Buchungen mit mehreren Tickets.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports ticket management for multi-traveller and multi-ticket bookings.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Subtenas biletadministradon por plurvojaĝantoj kaj plurbiletaj rezervoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite gestión de billetes para reservas de varios viajeros y de varios billetes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Mitme reisija ja mitme pileti reserveerimise piletihalduse toetus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bidaiari anizkoitzeko eta txartel anizkoitzeko erreserbetarako txartelak kudeatzeko euskarria du.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee useamman matkustajan tai matkalipun varausten lippujen hallintaa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de la gestion des billets pour les réservations multi-voyageurs et multi-billets.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Permite xestión de billetes diversos de varias persoas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תומך בניהול כרטיסים לריבוי נוסעים והזמנות עם ריבוי כרטיסים.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">बहु-यात्री और बहु-टिकट बुकिंग के लिए टिकट प्रबंधन का समर्थन करता है।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Többutasos és többjegyes foglalások jegykezelésének támogatása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Supporta gestion de billet per reservationes de multi-traveler e multi-ticket.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Mendukung pengelolaan tiket untuk multi-traveller dan pemesanan multi-tiket.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta la gestione dei biglietti per prenotazioni multi-viaggiatore e multi-biglietto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აქვს მრავალ-მოგზაურიანი და მრავალ-ბილეთიანი ჯავშნების მართვის მხარდაჭერა.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여행자가 여러 명이거나 여러 장의 표로 구성된 예약을 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor beheer van tickets voor meerdere reizigers en booking van meerdere tickets.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje zarządzanie biletami w przypadku rezerwacji u wielu przewoźników i wielu biletów.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a gestão de bilhetes para reservas multi-viajantes e multi-bilhetes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporta o gerenciamento de bilhetes para reservas de vários viajantes e multibancos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка управления работой с билетами для заказа с пересадками и одновременного заказа нескольких билетов.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">बहुयात्री-बहु-टिकट-बुकिंग्-कृते टिकट-प्रबन्धनस्य समर्थनं करोति ।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira upravljanje vozovnic za več potnikov in rezervacij za več vozovnic.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder biljetthantering för bokningar med flera resenärer och biljetter.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çok yolculu ve çok biletli rezervasyonlar için bilet yönetimi desteği.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка керування роботою з квитками для замовлень із пересадками та одночасного замовлення декількох квитків.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持管理多位旅客的多次订票。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援多人與多票券訂票的票券管理。</li>
      <li>Automatic booking data extraction from various input formats, performed locally on your device.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">استخراج آلي لبيانات الحجز من مختلف صيغ الإدخال، تُنفذ محليًا على جهازك.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Extracció automàtica de dades de les reserves des de diversos formats d'entrada, efectuades localment en el vostre dispositiu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Extracció automàtica de dades de les reserves des de diversos formats d'entrada, efectuades localment en el vostre dispositiu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Automatische Extraktion von Buchungsdaten aus verschiedenen Eingabeformaten, lokal auf Ihrem Gerät ausgeführt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Automatic booking data extraction from various input formats, performed locally on your device.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Aŭtomata rezervada eltiro de diversaj enigformatoj, farita loke sur via aparato.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Extracción automática de datos de reservas de diversos formatos de entrada, que se realiza localmente en su dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Reserveerimisandmete automaatne hankimine mitmesugustest sisendvormingutest, mis sooritatakse otse sinu seadmes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Hainbat sarrera-formatuetatik erreserba-datuak automatikoki erauztea, zure gailuan bertan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Automaattinen varaustiedon purku useista syötemuodoista paikallisesti omalla laitteellasi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Extraction automatique des données de réservation depuis de nombreux formats d'entrée, réalisée en local sur votre appareil.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Extracción automática de datos de billetes de varios formatos de entrada, executada localmente no seu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">חילוץ נתוני הזמנות אוטומטית ממגוון סוגי קלט, מבוצע מקומית במכשיר שלך.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">विभिन्न इनपुट प्रारूपों से स्वचालित बुकिंग डेटा निष्कर्षण, आपके डिवाइस पर स्थानीय रूप से किया जाता है।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Foglalási adatok automatikus kinyerése különböző bemeneti formátumokból, helyben, az Ön eszközén.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Extraction de datos de reservation automatic ex varie formatos de entrata, executate localmente sur tu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Ekstraksi data pemesanan otomatis dari berbagai format input, dilakukan secara lokal di perantimu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Estrazione automatica dei dati di prenotazione da vari formati di ingresso, eseguita localmente sul tuo dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ჯავშნის მონაცემების ავტომატური ამოღება მრავალი ფორმატიდან, რომელიც თქვენს მოწყობილობაზე ხდება.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 입력 자료에서 여정을 추출하며, 로컬 장치에서 이루어집니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Automatische extractie van bookinggegevens ui verschillende invoerformaten, lokaal uitgevoerd op uw apparaat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wydobywanie danych o rezerwacji z różnych formatów wejściowych, wykonywalne lokalnie na twoim urządzeniu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Extracção automática dos dados da reserva a partir de vários formatos de entrada, operando localmente no seu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração automática de dados de reserva de vários formatos de entrada, realizada localmente no seu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Автоматическое извлечение данных бронирования из различных входных форматов, которое происходит непосредственно на устройстве пользователя.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">विविधनिवेशस्वरूपेभ्यः स्वचालितं बुकिंगदत्तांशनिष्कासनं, यत् भवतः उपकरणे स्थानीयरूपेण क्रियते ।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Avtomatsko pridobivanje podatkov iz različnih vhodnih formatov lokalno v vaši napravi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Automatisk extrahering av bokningsinformation från diverse indataformat, utförd lokalt på din enhet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yerel olarak aygıtınızda gerçekleştirilen, çeşitli girdi biçimlerinden otomatik rezervasyon verisi çıkarımı.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичне видобування даних із різноманітних вхідних форматів, яке відбувається безпосередньо на вашому пристрої.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在设备端处理多种输入格式并自动提取预订数据。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">從多種輸入格式自動取出訂票資料，全部在您的裝置上進行而不會傳送到其他地方。</li>
      <li>Real-time delay and platform change information for trains.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">معلومات تأخير وتغيير منصات القطارات في الوقت الفعلي.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Informació d'endarreriments i canvis d'andana en temps real per als trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Informació d'endarreriments i canvis d'andana en temps real per als trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Echtzeitanzeige von Verspätungen und Gleisänderungen von Zügen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Real-time delay and platform change information for trains.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Realtempa prokrasto kaj platformoŝanĝaj informoj por trajnoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Retrasos e información de cambios de andén en tiempo real para trenes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rongide hilinemise ja platvormivahetuse reaalajas teave.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Trenen atzerapen eta nasa aldaketa informazioa denbora errealean.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tosiaikainen junien viivästys- ja laiturinmuutostieto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Informations de retard et de changement de quai en temps réel pour les trains.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Información de cambio de atraso e de plataforma de trens en tempo real.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">פרטי עיכובים והחלפות רציפים לרכבות.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">ट्रेनों के लिए वास्तविक समय विलंब और प्लेटफार्म परिवर्तन की जानकारी।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Valós idejű késés- és vágányinformációk vonatokhoz.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Information de retardo in tempo actual e cambiamento de platteforma per trainos. </li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Informasi penundaan real-time dan perubahan platform untuk kereta api.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Informazioni sui ritardi in tempo reale e sui cambi di binario per i treni.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლების დაყოვნებისა და პლატფორმის ცვლილების რეალურ დროში განახლება.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열차의 실시간 지연 정보와 승강장 변경을 표시합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Real-time informatie over vertraging en wijziging van perron voor treinen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dane w czasie rzeczywistym o opóźnieniach i zmianie peronów dla pociągów.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Informações em tempo-real de atrasos e mudança de plataformas nos comboios.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Atraso em tempo real e informações de mudança de plataforma para trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Информация о задержках и изменениях платформ для поездов.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">रेलयानानां कृते वास्तविकसमयविलम्बः, मञ्चपरिवर्तनस्य सूचना च।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Informacije o zamudah v realnem času in o spremembah peronov za vlake.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Information i realtid om fördröjningar och plattformsändringar för tåg.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Trenler için gerçek zamanlı gecikme ve platform değişikliği bilgisi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інформування про затримки та зміни платформ для потягів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">提供火车延误和站台变更的实时信息。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">火車的即時誤點或月台變更資訊。</li>
      <li>Weather forecast for destination along your trip.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">توقعات الطقس للوجهات على طول رحلتك.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Previsió meteorològica de la destinació durant el viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Previsió meteorològica del destí durant el viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Wettervorhersage für Orte entlang der Reiseroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Weather forecast for destination along your trip.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Veterprognozo por celloko dum via vojaĝo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Previsión meteorológica para el destino a lo largo de su viaje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ilmaennustus kogu reisi kohta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Helmugako eguraldiaren iragarpena bidaiatu bitartean.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kohteen sääennuste matkallesi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prévisions météorologiques pour la destination tout au long de votre voyage.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Prognóstico meteorolóxico do destino durante a viaxe.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תשקיפים ליעדים שלך לאורך הטיול.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">आपकी यात्रा के दौरान गंतव्य के लिए मौसम का पूर्वानुमान।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Időjárás-előrejelzés a kirándulás útvonalára.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Prevision Meteorologic per destination preter tu viage.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Ramalan cuaca untuk tujuan selama perjalananmu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Previsioni meteo per la destinazione lungo il tuo viaggio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ამინდის პროგნოზი დანიშნულების პუნქტისაკენ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여행지의 일기 예보를 표시합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Weersvoorspelling voor bestemming langs de reisroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Prognoza pogody dla miejsca docelowego podróży.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Previsão meteorológica no destino, ao longo da sua viagem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Previsão meteorológica para os destinos de sua viagem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Показ прогноза погоды в пункте назначения по ходу путешествия.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">भवतः यात्रायाः गन्तव्यस्थानस्य मौसमस्य पूर्वानुमानम्।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vremenska napoved za cilje ob vašem potovanju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Väderprognos för mål längs resan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yolculuk noktalarınız için hava durumu tahmini.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Показ прогнозу погоди у кінцевій точці вашої подорожі.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">显示旅途中各个目的地的天气预报。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">旅程上各目的地的天氣預報。</li>
      <li>Full control over all online access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تحكم كامل في جميع الوصولات عبر الإنترنت.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Control total sobre tots els accessos en línia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Control total sobre tots els accessos en línia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Vollständige Kontrolle über alle Online-Zugriffe.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Full control over all online access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Plena rego super ĉiu interreta aliro.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Control total sobre todos los accesos con conexión.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Täielik kontroll kogu võrgukasutuse üle.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Lerroko sarbide guzien kontrol osoa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Täysi hallinta kaikkeen verkkokäyttöön.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Contrôle complet sur tous les accès en ligne.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Control absoluto de todo o acceso por Internet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">שליטה מלאה בכל הגישה לאינטרנט.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">सभी ऑनलाइन पहुंच पर पूर्ण नियंत्रण।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Teljes ellenőrzés minden online hozzáférés felett.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Plen control sur omne accesso in linea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Kontrol penuh atas semua akses online.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Pieno controllo su tutti gli accessi in linea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ონლაინ წვდომის სრული კონტროლი.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">온라인 접근을 완전히 통제합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Volledige controle over alle online toegang.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Pełny nadzór nad dostępem do sieci.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Controlo total sobre todo o acesso 'online'.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Controle completo sobre todos os acessos online.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Полное управление всеми параметрами доступа в Интернет.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">सर्वेषां ऑनलाइन-प्रवेशस्य पूर्णं नियन्त्रणम्।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Popoln nadzor nad vsemi spletnimi dostopi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständig kontroll över alla nätåtkomster.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tüm çevrimiçi erişim üzerinde tam denetim.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Повне керування усіма параметрами доступу до інтернету.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">完全掌控所有在线功能。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對於所有線上存取的完整控制。</li>
      <li>Selection of alternative train connections on unbound tickets or on missed connections.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">اختيار وصلات قطار بديلة للتذاكر غير المقيدة أو في حالة فوات الوصلات.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Selecció de connexions alternatives de tren en bitllets independents o en connexions perdudes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Trieu les connexions alternatives de tren en bitllets independents o en connexions perdudes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Auswahl alternativer Zugverbindungen für Tickets ohne Zugbindung oder bei verpassten Anschlüssen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Selection of alternative train connections on unbound tickets or on missed connections.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Elekto de alternativaj trajnkonektoj sur nebinditaj biletoj aŭ ĉe sopiritaj konektoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Selección de conexiones de tren alternativas en billetes sin consolidar o en conexiones perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Alternatiivse rongiühenduse valimise võimalus näiteks piletite puudumise või mahajäämise korral.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Loturarik gabeko txarteletan edo galdutako konexioetan ordezko tren-konexioak hautatzea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vaihtoehtoisten junayhteyksien valinta, jos lippuja ei ole sidottu tai jatkoyhteys menetettiin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Sélection de correspondances ferroviaires alternatives pour les tickets non liés ou les correspondances manquées.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Selección de conexións alternativas de tren en billetes flexíbeis ou en caso de perda de conexións.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">בחירת החלפת רכבות חלופית על כרטיסים בין עירוניים והחלפות שהוחמצו.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">अनबाउंड टिकटों पर या छूटे हुए कनेक्शनों पर वैकल्पिक ट्रेन कनेक्शन का चयन।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Alternatív vonatjáratok kiválasztása a nem kötött menetjegyek vagy lekésett csatlakozások esetében.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Selection de connexiones alternative de traino sur billetes libere o sur connexiones mancate.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pemilihan koneksi kereta api alternatif untuk tiket tidak terikat atau koneksi yang terlewat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Selezione di collegamenti ferroviari alternativi su biglietti non vincolati o collegamenti persi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლების სხვა მიერთებების არჩევანის მხარდაჭერა გაუქმებული ბილეთების ან დაგვიანებული გადაჯდომის დროს.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열차를 놓쳤거나 자유 여정 승차권의 경우 대체 열차편 정보를 제공합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Selectie van alternatieve treinverbindingen op niet-gebonden tickets of over gemiste verbindingen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wybór zamiennych połączeń kolejowych dla nieprzypisanych biletów lub przegapionych połączeń.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Selecção de ligações de comboio alternativas para bilhetes não vinculados ou para ligações perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Seleção de conexões ferroviárias alternativas em bilhetes não consolidados ou em conexões perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Выбор альтернативных железнодорожных маршрутов при наличии проездного или опоздании на пересадку.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">अनबाउण्ड् टिकटेषु अथवा गम्यमानेषु संयोजनेषु वैकल्पिकरेलसंयोजनानां चयनम्।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Izbira alternativnih železniških povezav na nevezanih vozovnicah ali vozovnicah zamujenih povezav.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Val av alternativa tågförbindelser på öppna biljetter eller vid missade anslutningar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Açık biletler veya kaçırılan aktarmalar için alternatif tren önerileri seçimi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вибір альтернативних залізничних шляхів за умов наявності проїзного або неможливості з'єднання різних частин маршруту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">使用非绑定票券或错过联运交通时改签联运火车。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在使用未限制的票券或是沒趕上轉乘時可選取替代的火車轉乘。</li>
      <li>Local ground transportation navigation between elements of your itinerary.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">ملاحة للنقل البري المحلي بين عناصر مخطط رحلتك.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Navegació de transport local terrestre entre elements de l'itinerari.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Navegació de transport local terrestre entre elements de l'itinerari.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Lokale Navigation mit Bodenverkehr zwischen Abschnitten Ihres Reiseplans.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Local ground transportation navigation between elements of your itinerary.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Loka surtera transporta navigado inter elementoj de via itinero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Exploración de transporte terrestre local entre elementos de su itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kohaliku maismaatranspordi kasutamise võimalus reisi etappide vahel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Zure ibilbideko elementuen artean, lurreko tokiko garraioa nabigatzea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Paikallinen maaliikennenavigointi matkasuunnitelmasi osien välillä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Navigation à l'aide des transports en commun régionaux entre deux éléments de votre itinéraire.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Navegación de transporte terrestre local entre puntos do itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">ניווט בתחבורה קרקעית מקומית בין נקודות תוכנית המסע שלך.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">आपके यात्रा कार्यक्रम के तत्वों के बीच स्थानीय जमीनी परिवहन नेविगेशन।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Helyi földi közlekedési navigáció az útvonal elemei között.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Navigation de transportation de terra local inter elementos de tu itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Navigasi transportasi darat lokal antara elemen rencana perjalananmu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Navigazione del trasporto via terra locale tra gli elementi del tuo itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ადგილობრივი სახმელეთო ტრანსპორტირების ნავიგაცია თქვენი მარშრუტის ელემენტებს შორის.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여행 중에 이용할 지역 대중 교통 정보를 제공합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Lokale navigatie van vervoer op de grond tussen elementen van uw reisroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Lokalne przemieszczanie się naziemne pomiędzy elementami twojego planu podróży.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Navegação local em transportes terrestres entre elementos do seu itinerário.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Navegação por transporte terrestre local entre elementos do seu itinerário. </li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Навигация по местному наземному транспорту между фрагментами маршрута.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">भवतः यात्रासूचनायाः तत्त्वानां मध्ये स्थानीयं भूपरिवहनयानयात्रा।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Lokalna navigacija po zemeljskih prevozi med elementi vašega plana potovanja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Navigering för lokal marktransport mellan delar av resplanen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yolcu belgesi ögeleriniz arasında yerel yer ulaşımı dolaşımı.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Навігація на місцевості під час пересадок між фрагментами вашого маршруту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在各段行程间为您进行本地地面交通导航。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在您的旅行計劃項目之間的本地地面運輸導覽。</li>
      <li>Train coach layout view (for some operators only).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">عرض تخطيط عربات القطار (لبعض المشغلين فقط).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista de la disposició de vagons del tren (només per a alguns operadors).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la disposició de vagons del tren (només per a alguns operadors).</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Ansicht der Wagenreihung von Zügen (nur für einige Betreiber).</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Train coach layout view (for some operators only).</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Trajna vagona enpaĝigvido (nur por kelkaj funkciigistoj).</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista del esquema del tren (solo para algunos operadores).</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Tren bagoiaren antolaeraren ikuspegia (operatzaile batzuetan bakarrik).</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Junien vaunukarttanäkymä (joillekin operaattoreille).</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Affichage des compositions des trains (pour certains opérateurs uniquement)</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Vista do plano do coche de tren (só para algúns operadores).</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">תצוגת פריסת אזור ברכבת (אצל חלק מהמפעילים בלבד).</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">ट्रेन कोच लेआउट दृश्य (केवल कुछ ऑपरेटरों के लिए)।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Vonatalaprajz nézet (csak egyes szolgáltatók esetén).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Vista de disposition de carrossa (solment eper alcun operatores)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tampilan tata letak gerbong kereta (hanya untuk beberapa operator).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Vista della disposizione della carrozza del treno (solo per alcuni operatori).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის ვაგონში ადგილების დათვალიერება (მხოლოდ ზოგიერთი ოპერატორისთვის).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열차 객차 구성 보기(일부 철도 사업자만).</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Weergave van indeling treinwagons (alleen voor sommige vervoerders)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Widok układu wagonu kolejowego (tylko dla wybranych przewoźników).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Área de disposição dos lugares do comboio (apenas com alguns operadores).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização do layout do vagão (somente para alguns operadores).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Просмотр мест в вагоне поезда (только для некоторых операторов).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">रेलयानस्य कोचविन्यासदृश्यं (केवलं केषाञ्चन संचालकानाम् कृते)।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pogled postavitve vlaka (samo za nekatere operaterje).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tågvagnslayout (bara för vissa operatörer).</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tren vagonu yerleşimi görünümü (yalnızca bazı operatörlerde).</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перегляд місць у вагоні потягу (лише для деяких операторів).</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">列车编组视图 (仅限某些运营商)。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視火車車廂內部配置（僅部分交通機構）。</li>
      <li>Train station and airport per-floor maps based on OpenStreetMap data.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">خرائط محطات القطار والمطارات لكل طابق بناءً على بيانات OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mapes per planta de l'estació de tren i l'aeroport basats en les dades d'OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mapes per planta de l'estació de tren i l'aeroport basats en les dades d'OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Geschosskarten von Bahnhöfen und Flughäfen basierend auf OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Train station and airport per-floor maps based on OpenStreetMap data.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Trajna stacidomo kaj flughaveno po-etaĝaj mapoj bazitaj sur OpenStreetMap-datenoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Planos de las plantas de estaciones de tren y de aeropuertos basados en datos de OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Tren geltokiko eta aireportuko solairukako mapak, «OpenStreetMap»ako datuetan oinarrituta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">OpenStreetMapin tietoon perustuvat rautatie- ja lentoasemien kerroskartat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les cartes de gares et d'aéroports s'appuyant sur les données de OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Mapas das plantas de estacións de tren e de aeroportos baseados en datos de OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">מפות תחנות רכבת ונמלי תעופה לפי קומות על בסיס הנתונים מ־OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">ओपनस्ट्रीटमैप डेटा पर आधारित रेलवे स्टेशन और हवाई अड्डे के प्रति-मंजिल मानचित्र।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Az OpenStreetMap adatain alapuló, emeletenkénti vasútállomási és repülőtéri térképek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Mappas per plano de  Station de traino e aeroporto basate sur datos de OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Peta stasiun kereta dan bandara per lantai berdasarkan data OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Mappe per piano di stazioni ferroviarie e aeroporti basate sui dati di OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">რკინიგზის სადგურებისა და აეროპორტების სართულების რუკა OpenStreetMap -ზე დაყრდნობით.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">OpenStreetMap 데이터를 사용하는 기차역과 공항 층별 지도 보기.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kaarten per verdieping van station en luchthaven gebaseerd op gegevens uit OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Plany pięter dworców kolejowych i lotnisk na podstawie danych z OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mapas das estações de comboio e aeroportos por pisos, baseados em dados do OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Mapas de estações de trem e aeroportos por andar com base em dados do OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поэтажные карты железнодорожных станций и аэропортов на основе данных OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">OpenStreetMap आँकडानां आधारेण रेलस्थानकस्य विमानस्थानकस्य च प्रतितलस्य मानचित्रम् ।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zemljevidi železniške postaje in letališča po nadstropjih na podlagi podatkov OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tågstations- och flygplatskartor för varje våning baserade på data från OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">OpenStreetMap verisine dayalı tren istasyonu ve havaalanı kat haritaları.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Мапи поверхів залізничних станцій та аеропортів засновано на даних OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">基于 OpenStreetMap 数据的火车站地图和机场多层地图。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">基於 OpenStreetMap 資料的火車站與機場各樓層地圖。</li>
      <li>Available dock-based or free-floating rental bikes can be displayed on the train station map.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">يمكن عرض الدراجات المستأجرة المتوفرة (المثبتة في محطات أو الحرة) على خريطة محطة القطار.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Les bicicletes de lloguer disponibles ancorades o flotants es poden mostrar en el mapa de l'estació de tren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Les bicicletes de lloguer disponibles ancorades o flotants es poden mostrar en el mapa de l'estació de tren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Anzeige von verfügbaren Leihfahrrädern – sowohl mit als auch ohne Verleihstation – auf Bahnhofskarten.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Available dock-based or free-floating rental bikes can be displayed on the train station map.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Disponeblaj dok-bazitaj aŭ liber-flosantaj lubicikloj povas esti montritaj sur la fervoja stacidoma mapo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Las bicicletas de alquiler disponibles en base o sin ella se pueden mostrar en el mapa de la estación de tren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Alokairuko bizikleta erabilgarriak, nasa-oinarrikoak edo higikorrak, tren-geltokiko mapan azal daitezke.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Saatavilla olevat vapaat potkulaudat tai vuokrapyörät voidaan näyttää rautatieaseman kartalla.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les vélos de location disponibles en libre service ou en station d'accueil peuvent être affichés sur la carte des gares. </li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">As bicicletas de alugamento dispoñíbeis, en puntos de aparcamento ou fóra deles, poden amosarse nos mapas das estacións de tren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">אפשר להציג אופניים עגונים או משוחררים להשכרה על מפת תחנת הרכבת.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">उपलब्ध डॉक-आधारित या फ्री-फ्लोटिंग किराये की बाइकों को रेलवे स्टेशन के मानचित्र पर प्रदर्शित किया जा सकता है।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Szabad dokkolós vagy szabadon szállítható kölcsönözhető kerékpárok megjelenítése a vasútállomások térképein.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Bicyclettas disponibile de locar basate sur bassino o libere de flottar pote esser monstrate sur le mappa de station de traino.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Penyewaan sepeda dock-based atau free-floating yang tersedia dapat ditampilkan di peta stasiun kereta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Le biciclette a noleggio disponibili su rastrelliera o a flusso libero possono essere visualizzate sulla mappa della stazione ferroviaria.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის სადგურის რუკაზე შეგიძლიათ დოკზე ბაზირებული ან თავისუფლად მოსრიალე გაქირავებადი ველოსიპედები გაჩვენოთ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">기차역 지도에 고정 스테이션에 있거나 고정되어 있지 않은 렌탈 자전거를 표시할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Beschikbare huurfietsen in stalling en vrijstaand kan getoond worden op de kaart van het treinstation.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dostępne rowery do wypożyczenia w systemie ze stacjami lub bez nich, można wyświetlić na mapie dworca kolejowego.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Poderá mostrar as bicicletas de aluguer com bloqueios ou livres no mapa das estações dos correios.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">As bicicletas de aluguel disponíveis em docas ou avulsas podem ser exibidas no mapa da estação de trem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">На карте железнодорожной станции могут быть показаны доступные прокатныевелосипеды со стационарной или произвольной парковкой.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">उपलब्धानि गोदी-आधारितानि अथवा मुक्त-प्लवमानानि किराया-द्विचक्रिकाः रेलस्थानकस्य मानचित्रे प्रदर्शयितुं शक्यन्ते ।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Razpoložljiva kolesa za najem na stebričkih ali prosto dostopna kolesa na zemljevidu železniške postaje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tillgängliga stationsbaserade eller fristående hyrcyklar kan visas på tågstationskartan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tren istasyonu haritasında rıhtımlı veya serbest bırakılmış kiralık bisiklet bilgisi görüntülenebilir.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">На мапі залізничної станції може бути показано доступні орендовані велосипеди зі стаціонарними або довільними місцями паркування.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">火车站地图显示空余的有桩或无桩共享单车。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在火車站地圖上可以顯示可用的腳踏車租借，支援停車柱式或是自由停靠的腳踏車租借。</li>
      <li>Personal travel statistics to monitor environmental impact.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إحصاءات السفر الشخصية لمراقبة التأثير البيئي.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Estadístiques de viatges personals per a controlar l'impacte ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Estadístiques de viatges personals per a controlar l'impacte ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Persönliche Reisestatistik zur Auswertung des Einflusses auf die Umwelt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Personal travel statistics to monitor environmental impact.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Personaj vojaĝaj statistikoj por monitori median efikon.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Estadísticas de viaje personales para monitorizar el impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Isiklik reisistatistika oma ökoloogilise jalajälje selgitamiseks.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bidaia pertsonalen estatistikak ingurumen eragina gainbegiratzeko.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Matkan henkilökohtaiset tilastot ympäristövaikutusten tarkkailemiseksi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Statistiques de voyages personnels pour calculer l'impact environnemental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Estatísticas de viaxe persoal para facer seguimento do impacto medioambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">סטטיסטיקת נסועה אישית למעקב אחר ההשפעה על איכות הסביבה.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hi">पर्यावरणीय प्रभाव की निगरानी के लिए व्यक्तिगत यात्रा आँकड़े।</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Személyes utazási statisztikák a környezeti hatások nyomon követésére.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Statistica de viage personal a supervisionar impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Statistik perjalanan pribadi untuk memantau dampak lingkungan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Statistiche di viaggio personali per monitorare l'impatto ambientale.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მოგზაურობის სტატისტიკა გარემოზე ეფექტის მონიტორინგისთვის.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">환경 영향을 계산하는 개인 여행 통계 정보를 제공합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Persoonlijke reisstatistieken om impact op de omgeving te monitoren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Osobisty statystyki podróżowania do monitorowania wpływu na środowisko.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Estatísticas pessoais da viagem para acompanhar o impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Estatísticas pessoais da viagem para monitorar o impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Личная статистика путешествий для наблюдения за воздействием на окружающую среду.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sa">पर्यावरणप्रभावस्य निरीक्षणार्थं व्यक्तिगतयात्रासांख्यिकी।</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Osebna statistika potovanj za spremljanje vplivov na okolje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Personlig resestatistik för att övervaka miljöpåverkan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çevre etkisini izlemek üzere kişisel yolculuk istatistikleri.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Особиста статистика подорожей для стеження за впливом на навколишнє середовище.</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">个人旅行统计数据，可观察您对环境的影响。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">個人旅行統計資料，讓您追蹤自己的環境影響。</li>
    </ul>
    <p>KDE Itinerary works best alongside KMail's itinerary extraction plug-in and KDE Connect, or Nextcloud Hub and DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">يعمل مخطط رحلة كيدي بشكل أفضل جنبًا إلى جنب مع إضافة استخراج المخطط في KMail و KDE Connect، أو Nextcloud Hub و DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Itinerary funciona millor amb el connector d'extracció d'itineraris del KMail i el KDE Connect, o el Nextcloud Hub i el DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Itinerary funciona millor amb el connector d'extracció d'itineraris de KMail i KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub i DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KDE-Itinerary funktioniert am besten in Verbindung mit KMails Itinerary-Extraktionsmodulen und KDE Connect, oder mit Nextcloud Hub und DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Itinerary works best alongside KMail's itinerary extraction plug-in and KDE Connect, or Nextcloud Hub and DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KDE-Itinero funkcias plej bone kune kun la aldonaĵo de KMail-eltiro de itinero kaj KDE Connect, aŭ Nextcloud Hub kaj DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary funciona mejor con el complemento de extracción de itinerarios de KMail y con KDE Connect, o con Nextcloud Hub y DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KDE Itineraar töötab kõige paremini koos KMaili reisikava hankimise plugina ja KDE Connectiga või ka Nextcloudi ja DavDroidiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«KDE Itinerary» hobe dabil «KMail»en ibilbidea erauzteko pluginarekin eta «KDE Connect» edo «Nextcloud Hub» eta «DavDroid»ekin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KDE Itinerary toimii parhaiten yhdessä KMailin matkasuunnitelmatietoliitännäisen ja KDE Connectin tai Nextcloud Hubin ja DavDroidin kanssa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDE Itinerary fonctionne au maximum de ses capacités avec le module d'extraction des itinéraires de KMail et KDEConnect mais aussi avec Nextcloud Hub et DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KDE Itinerary funciona mellor co complemento de extracción de itinerario de KMail e KDE Connect, ou Nextcloud Hub e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">KDE Itinerary עובד הכיטוב לצד תוסף חילוץ תוכניות הנסיעה KMailו־KDE Connect או Nextcloud Hub ו־DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hi">केडीई यात्रा कार्यक्रम, केमेल के यात्रा कार्यक्रम निष्कर्षण प्लग-इन और केडीई कनेक्ट, या नेक्स्टक्लाउड हब और डेवड्रॉइड के साथ मिलकर सबसे अच्छा काम करता है।</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KDE Itinerary a legjobban a KMail itinerkinyerő bővítménye és a KDE Connect vagy a Nextcloud Hub és DavDroid mellett működik.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KDE Itinerary functiona meliormente  con plugin de extraction de itinerario de KMail e KDE Connect, o Hub de Nextcloud e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KDE Itinerary bekerja paling baik dengan plugin itinerary extraction KMail dan KDE Connect, atau Nextcloud Hub dan DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary funziona meglio insieme all'estensione di estrazione degli itinerari di KMail e KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KDE Itinerarary ყველაზე კარგად KMail-ის დამატებასთან, KDE Connect-თან, Nextcloud Hub-თან და DavDroid-თან მუშაობს.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDE 여행 정보는 KMail의 여행 정보 추천 플러그인, KDE Connect, Nextcloud 허브 및 DavDroid와 같이 작동합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary werkt het best naast de plug-in voor reisroute uitpakken van KMail en KDE Connect of Nextcloud Hub en DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KDE Itinerary działa najlepiej wraz z wtyczką do wydobywania itinerary dla KMaila oraz KDE Connect, lub Nextcloud Hub i DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Itinerary funciona melhor com o 'plugin' de extracção de itinerários e com o KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub ou o DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDE Itinerary funciona melhor junto com o plugin de extração de itinerário do KMail e KDE Connect ou Nextcloud Hub e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Программа «Маршруты KDE» лучше всего работает с модулем извлечения маршрутов KMail и KDE Connect или Nextcloud Hub и DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sa">KDE यात्रासूची KMail इत्यस्य यात्रासूचीनिष्कासनप्लग-इन् तथा KDE Connect, अथवा Nextcloud Hub तथा DavDroid इत्येतयोः पार्श्वे सर्वोत्तमरूपेण कार्यं करोति ।</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KDE Itinerary deluje najbolje skupaj z dodatki z vtičnikom za ekstrakcijo podatkov v KMail in KDE Connect ali Nextcloud Hub in DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan fungerar bäst tillsammans med Kmails insticksprogram för extrahering av resplan och KDE-anslut, eller Nextcloud-navet och DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KDE Yol Kılavuzu, en iyi olarak K Posta’nın yolculuk belgesi çıkarma eklentisi ve KDE Bağlan, Nextcloud Hub veya DavDroid ile birlikte çalışır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary найкраще працює із додатком видобування даних KMail та KDE Connect або Nextcloud Hub і DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Itinerary 是 KMail 行程提取插件和 KDE Connect 的最佳搭档，还能配合 Nextcloud Hub 和 DavDroid 使用。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">《KDE 旅行計劃》在與 KMail 的旅行計劃取出外掛程式、KDE Connect 或是 Nextcloud Hub 及 DavDroid 共同使用時更方便。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Timeline view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض الخط الزمني</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la línia de temps</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la línia de temps</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled časové osy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Zeitleistenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Timeline view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Templinio vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista cronológica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Denbora-lerro ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Aikajananäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue chronologique.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista cronolóxica.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת ציר זמן</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">समयरेखा दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Idővonal nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de Chronologia.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan linimasa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista della linea temporale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">დროის ხაზის ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">타임라인 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Tijdlijnweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok osi czasu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista cronológica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição cronológica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр расписания</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">समयरेखादृश्यम्</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled časovnice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tidslinjevisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Zaman akışı görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">时间线视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">時間軸檢視</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-timeline.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Boarding pass view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض بطاقة الصعود إلى الطائرة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de les targetes d'embarcament</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de les targetes d'embarcament</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled na nástupní doklad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Bordkartenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Boarding pass view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Vido de enirado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de tarjetas de embarque</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ontziratze-txartel ikuspegia.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Maihinnousukorttinäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage de la carte d'embarquement.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista de pase de embarque.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת כרטיס עלייה לאמצעי התחבורה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">बोर्डिंग पास दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Beszállókártya nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de carta de imbarcar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan boarding pass</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista delle carte d'imbarco</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">თვითმფრინავის ბილეთის ნახვა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">탑승권 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Boardingpasweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok kart odpraw</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista do cartão de embarque</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização do cartão de embarque</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр посадочных талонов</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">बोर्डिंग पास दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled vstopnega kupona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Visning av boardingkort</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Biniş kartı görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд посадкових квитків</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">登机牌视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">登機證檢視</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-boardingpass.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Train layout view highlighting the coach with a seat reservation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض تخطيط القطار مع إبراز العربة التي تحتوي على حجز مقعد</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la disposició del tren amb ressaltat del vagó amb una reserva de seient</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la disposició del tren amb ressaltat del vagó amb una reserva de seient</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Wagenreihungsansicht mit Hervorhebung des Wagens mit Sitzplatzreservierung</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Train layout view highlighting the coach with a seat reservation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Trajna aranĝo vido elstarigante la trejniston kun sidloko rezervado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista del esquema del tren resaltando el coche con reserva de asiento</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tren antolamenduaren ikuspegia, eserleku-erreserba duen bagoia nabarmenduta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Varatun paikan korostava junan vaunukartta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage de la composition du train, détaillant la voiture où le siège est réservé.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista de mapa de tren que realza o coche coa reserva de asento.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת פריסת רכבת מדגישה את האזור עם המושבים שהוזמנו</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">सीट आरक्षण वाले कोच को हाइलाइट करते हुए ट्रेन लेआउट दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Vonat alaprajza a helyfoglalással rendelkező kocsit kiemelve</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Dispoition de traino evidentiante le carrossa con un reservation de placia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan tata letak kereta yang menyoroti gerbong dengan reservasi kursi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista della disposizione del treno che evidenzia la carrozza con la prenotazione di un posto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის განლაგების ხედი სავარძლის რეზერვაციის გამოკვეთით</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">예약한 열차 좌석이 강조된 열차 구성 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Treinindelingsweergave met accentuering van het rijtuig met een zitplaats reservering</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok układu pociągu z rezerwacją miejsc</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Área de disposição dos comboios que realça o lugar com uma reserva</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização do layout do trem destacando o vagão com reserva de assento</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр мест в вагонах поезда с подсветкой вагона с забронированным местом</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">आसनआरक्षणेन सह कोचं प्रकाशयन् रेलविन्यासदृश्यम्</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled postavitve vlaka s poudarjenim vagonom in rezervacijo sedeža</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tågplatsvisning som färglägger vagnen med platsbokning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Koltuk rezervasyonunu vurgulayan vagon görünümlü tren yerleşimi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Панель місць у вагонах потягу із підсвічуванням заброньованих місць</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">列车编组视图，高亮显示了车厢中预订的座位</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">火車佈局檢視，突顯座位預約與車廂</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-vehicle-layout.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Train station platform map, highlighting arrival and departure platforms</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">خريطة منصة محطة القطار، مع إبراز منصات الوصول والمغادرة</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Mapa d'andanes de l'estació de tren, destacant les andanes d'arribada i sortida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mapa d'andanes de l'estació de tren, destacant les andanes d'arribada i eixida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Bahnhofsgleiskarte mit Hervorhebung des Ankunft- und Abfahrtgleises</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Train station platform map, highlighting arrival and departure platforms</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Performmapo de fervoja stacidomo, elstarigante alvenajn kaj forirajn kajojn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Mapa de andenes de estación de tren, resaltando andenes de llegada y salida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tren-geltokiaren nasaren mapa, iristeko eta irteteko nasak nabarmenduz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Lähtö- ja saapumislaitureita korostava rautatieasemakartta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La carte des quais de gare, détaillant les quais d'arrivée et de départ.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Mapa da plataforma da estación de tren que realza as plataformas de chegada e de saída.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">מפת רציפי תחנת הרכבת, עם הדגשה על רציפי הגעה ויציאה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">रेलवे स्टेशन के प्लेटफार्म का नक्शा, जिसमें आगमन और प्रस्थान प्लेटफार्म को दर्शाया गया है</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Vasútállomás vágánytérképe, kiemelve az érkező és induló peronokat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Mappa de platteforma de station de traino, evidentiante platteformas de arrivata e partita</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Peta platform stasiun kereta, menyoroti platform kedatangan dan keberangkatan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Mappa dei binari della stazione ferroviaria, evidenziando i binari di arrivo e partenza</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის სადგურის პლატფორმების რუკა, ჩამომსვლელი და გასამგზავრებელი პლატფორმების გამოკვეთით</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">출발 및 도착 승강장을 강조한 기차역 승강장 지도</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Perronkaart van treinstation, accentuering van aankomst- en vertrekperrons</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Plan peronu dworca kolejowego, podświetlający perony przybycia i odjazdu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Mapa das plataformas das estações de comboio que realça as plataformas de partidas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Mapa da plataforma da estação de trem, destacando as plataformas de chegada e partida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Карта платформ железнодорожной станции с подсветкой платформ прибытия и отправления</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">रेलस्थानकस्य मञ्चनक्शा, आगमनप्रस्थानमञ्चान् प्रकाशयति</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Zemljevid perona železniške postaje s poudarkom na peronih za prihod in odhod</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tågstationskarta för plattformar, som markerar ankomst- och avgångsplattformar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Varış ve kalkış platformlarını vurgulayan tren istasyonu platform haritası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Мапа платформ залізничної станції, підсвічування платформ прибуття та відправлення</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">火车站站台地图，高亮显示了入站和出站站台</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">火車站月台地圖，突顯抵達和出發的月台</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-train-station-platform-map.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Train station map showing real-time availability of rental bikes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">خريطة محطة القطار التي تعرض توفر الدراجات المستأجرة في الوقت الفعلي</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Mapa de l'estació de tren que mostra la disponibilitat en temps real de les bicicletes de lloguer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mapa de l'estació de tren que mostra la disponibilitat en temps real de les bicicletes de lloguer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Bahnhofskarte mit Anzeige der Echtzeitverfügbarkeit von Leihfahrrädern</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Train station map showing real-time availability of rental bikes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Mapo de la fervoja stacidomo montrante realtempan haveblecon de lubicikloj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Mapa de estación de tren mostrando la disponibilidad de bicicletas de alquiler en tiempo real</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tren-geltokiko mapa, alokairuko bizikleten eskuragarritasuna denbora errealean erakusten duena.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Rautatieasemakartta näyttää tosiaikaiset vuokrapolkupyörätiedot</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La carte de la gare ferroviaire affichant la disponibilité en temps réel des vélos de location.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Mapa de estación de tren que amosa a dispoñibilidade de bicicletas de alugamento en tempo real.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">מפת תחנות הרכבת מציגה זמינות של אופניים להשכרה בזמן אמת</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">रेलवे स्टेशन का नक्शा किराये पर बाइक की वास्तविक समय उपलब्धता दर्शाता है</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Vasútállomás térképe, valós időben megjelenítve a kölcsönözhető kerékpárok elérhetőségét</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Mappa de station de traino monstrante disponibilitate in tempore actual de bicyclettas a locar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Peta stasiun kereta api yang menunjukkan ketersediaan sepeda rental secara real-time.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Mappa della stazione ferroviaria che mostra la disponibilità in tempo reale delle biciclette a noleggio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">რკინიგზის სადგური გასაქირავებელი ველოსიპედების რეალურ დროში ჩვენებით</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">실시간 렌탈 자전거 상황을 표시하는 기차역 지도</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Kaart van treinstation met werkelijk beschikbare huurfietsen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Plan dworca kolejowego, pokazujący w czasie rzeczywistym dostępność rowerów do wypożyczenia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Mapa das estações de comboios que mostra a disponibilidade em tempo-real das bicicletas de aluguer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Mapa da estação de trem mostrando a disponibilidade em tempo real de aluguel de bicicletas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Карта железнодорожной станции с показом доступности прокатных велосипедов в режиме реального времени</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">किरायाद्विचक्रिकाणां वास्तविकसमये उपलब्धतां दर्शयति रेलस्थानकस्य मानचित्रम्</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Zemljevid železniške postaje sproti prikazuje razpoložljivost koles za najem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tågstationskarta som visar tillgängliga hyrcyklar i realtid.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kiralık bisikletlerin kullanılabilirliğini gösteren tren istasyonu haritası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Мапа залізничної станції із показом доступності оренди велосипедів у режимі реального часу</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">显示出租自行车实时信息的火车站地图。</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">火車站地圖，顯示租借腳踏車的即時可用狀態</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-train-station-map-with-rental-bike-data.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Detailed information for the select entity on the train station map</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">معلومات مفصلة للكيان المحدد على خريطة محطة القطار</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Informació detallada de l'entitat seleccionada en el mapa de l'estació de tren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Informació detallada de l'entitat seleccionada en el mapa de l'estació de tren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Detaillierte Informationen des ausgewählten Elements auf der Bahnhofskarte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Detailed information for the select entity on the train station map</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Detalaj informoj por la elektita ento sur la mapo de fervoja stacidomo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Información detallada para la entidad seleccionada en el mapa de la estación de tren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Hautatutako erakundearen informazio zehatza tren-geltokiko mapan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Yksityiskohtainen tieto rautatieasemakartalta valitusta kohteesta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Informations détaillées pour l'entité sélectionnée sur la carte de la gare.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Información detallada da entidade seleccionada no mapa da estación de tren.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">מידע מפורט על הישות הנבחרת במפת תחנת הרכבות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">रेलवे स्टेशन के नक्शे पर चयनित इकाई के लिए विस्तृत जानकारी</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Részletes információk a vasútállomás térképén kiválasztott entitásról</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Information detaliate per le entitate de seliger sur le mappa de station de traino</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Informasi mendetail untuk entitas yang dipilih di peta stasiun kereta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Informazioni dettagliate per l'entità selezionata sulla mappa della stazione ferroviaria</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">რკინიგზის სადგურზე მონიშნული ელემენტის დეტალური ინფორმაცია</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">기차역 지도에서 선택한 항목의 자세한 정보</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Gedetailleerde informatie voor het te selecteren item op kaart van het treinstation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Szczegółowe nt. wybranego obiektu na planie dworca kolejowego</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Informações detalhadas para a entidade de selecção no mapa das estações de comboios</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Informação detalhada para a entidade selecionada no mapa da estação de trem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Подробные сведения о выбранном объекте на карте железнодорожной станции</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">रेलस्थानकस्य मानचित्रे चयनितस्य सत्तायाः विस्तृतसूचना</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Podrobne informacije za izbrani predmet na zemljevidu železniške postaje</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Detaljerad information om objektet som valts på tågstationskartan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Tren istasyonu haritasında seçili varlık için ayrıntılı bilgi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Докладні відомості для позначеного пункту на мапі залізничної станції</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">火车站地图，显示了所选条目的详细信息</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">在火車站地圖中對於所選項目的詳細資訊</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-train-station-map-details.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Travel statistics view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ar">عرض إحصاءات السفر</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de les estadístiques dels viatges</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de les estadístiques dels viatges</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled na statistiky cestování</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Reisestatistikansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Travel statistics view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Vido de Vojaĝstatistikoj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de estadísticas de viajes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Bidai-estatistiken ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Matkan tilastonäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage des statistiques de voyages.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista de estatísticas de viaxe.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת סטטיסטיקת נסיעה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hi">यात्रा सांख्यिकी दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Utazási statisztika nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de statistica de viage</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan statistik perjalanan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista delle statistiche di viaggio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მოგზაურობის სტატისტიკის ნახვა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">여행 통계 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Weergave reisstatistieken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok statystyki podróży</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Área de estatísticas de viagens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização de estatísticas da viagem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр статистики путешествий</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sa">यात्रा सांख्यिकी दृश्य</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled potovalne statistike</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Visning av resestatistik</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Yolculuk istatistikleri görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Панель статистики подорожей</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">旅程统计数据视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">旅行統計資料檢視</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-statistics.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <url type="homepage">https://apps.kde.org/itinerary</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=KDE+Itinerary</url>
  <url type="donation">https://www.kde.org/community/donations/?app=itinerary&amp;source=appdata</url>
  <url type="vcs-browser">https://invent.kde.org/pim/itinerary</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>itinerary</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.itinerary.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="25.12.2" date="2026-02-05">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Restore global menu drawer in mobile mode.</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Restauración del cajón de menú global en modo móvil.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Restaura a gaveta do menu global no modo móvel.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Восстановлена поддержка глобального меню в мобильном режиме;</li>
          <li>Fix manual entrance of certain flight numbers.</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Se ha corregido la entrada manual de ciertos números de vuelo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigida a entrada manual de determinados números de voo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен ручной ввод некоторых номеров рейсов;</li>
          <li>Support SNCF TER passes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Compatibilidad con pases TER de la SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a passes SNCF TER.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка проездных SNCF TER;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.12.1" date="2026-01-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for booking.com, České dráhy, DB, gomus, KLM and MÁV.</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Nuevos o mejorados extractores de documentos de viaje para booking.com, České dráhy, DB, gomus, KLM y MÁV.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para booking.com, České dráhy, DB, gomus, KLM e MÁV.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули получения информации о документах о путешествиях для booking.com, České dráhy, DB, gomus, KLM и MÁV;</li>
          <li>Fix crash on referenced but non-existent PDF masks (bug 513945).</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema que causava o fechamento inesperado do programa em máscaras de PDF referenciadas, mas inexistentes (bug 513945).</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено аварийное завершение при ссылках на несуществующие маски PDF (ошибка 513945);</li>
          <li>Fixes for online post-processing reservations without geographic coordinates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correções para reservas online pós-processadas sem coordenadas geográficas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправления для онлайн-постобработки бронирований без географических координат;</li>
          <li>Fixes for sort order corner cases in the timeline view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correções para casos extremos de ordenação na visualização da linha do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправления крайних случаев порядка сортировки в представлении временной шкалы;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.12.0" date="2025-12-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Built-in currency converter.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Conversor de moedas integrado.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Встроенный конвертер валют;</li>
          <li>Journey searches starting from the current location.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pesquisas de trechos a partir da localização atual.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поиск маршрутов от текущего местоположения;</li>
          <li>Simplified journey search UI.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Interface de busca de trechos simplificada.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Упрощённый интерфейс поиска маршрутов;</li>
          <li>Displaying altitude information in live status view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição de informações de altitude na visualização de status em tempo real.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Отображение информации о высоте в режиме реального времени;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.08.3" date="2025-11-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Căile Ferate Române, citycity.se, Comboios de Portugal, Flixbus, Müpa Budapest, NH Hotels, Ryanair, United and ZSSK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou melhorados para Căile Ferate Române, citycity.se, Comboios de Portugal, Flixbus, Müpa Budapest, NH Hotels, Ryanair, United e ZSSK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения проездных документов для Căile Ferate Române, citycity.se, Comboios de Portugal, Flixbus, Müpa Budapest, NH Hotels, Ryanair, United и ZSSK;</li>
          <li>Fix performance issues and hangs with the journey search result view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção de problemas de desempenho e travamentos na visualização dos resultados da pesquisa de viagens.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены проблемы с производительностью и зависания в представлении результатов поиска маршрутов;</li>
          <li>Fix parsing of ÖBB onboard speed data.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da análise dos dados de velocidade a bordo da ÖBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен анализ данных скорости ÖBB на борту;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.08.2" date="2025-10-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for AirAsia, B&amp;B Hotels, Booking.com, Ethiad, Ryanair, SNCF and tixly.</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Nuevos o mejorados extractores de documentos de viaje para AirAsia, hoteles B&amp;B, Booking.com, Ethiad, Ryanair, SNCF y tixly.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para AirAsia, B&amp;B Hotels, Booking.com, Etihad, Ryanair, SNCF e Tixly.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные средства извлечения документов о поездках для AirAsia, B&amp;B Hotels, Booking.com, Ethiad, Ryanair, SNCF и tixly;</li>
          <li>Position journey result view at the end when searching by arrival time.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">A visualização dos resultados da viagem é exibida ao final da pesquisa por horário de chegada.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Позиционирование представления результатов маршрута в конце при поиске по времени прибытия;</li>
          <li>Fixed parsing of certain Apple Wallet pass variants.</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Se ha corregido el análisis de ciertas variantes de pases de Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na análise de determinadas variantes dos passes do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен анализ синтаксиса некоторых вариантов пропусков Apple Wallet;</li>
          <li>Fixed scaling artifacts in public transport line icons.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigidos problemas de escala nos ícones das linhas de transporte público.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены артефакты масштабирования в значках линий общественного транспорта;</li>
          <li>Fixed parsing intermediate stops from Railteam.</li>
          <li xml:lang="es">Se ha corregido el análisis de paradas intermedias de Railteam.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na análise de paradas intermediárias do Railteam.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен анализ промежуточных остановок от Railteam;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.08.1" date="2025-09-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for booking.com, Center Parcs, Coloseum, eDreams, Finnair, LTG Link, MÁV, Pretix, RegioJet, Thalys and United Airlines.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para booking.com, Center Parcs, Coloseum, eDreams, Finnair, LTG Link, MÁV, Pretix, RegioJet, Thalys e United Airlines.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные анализаторы документов поездок для booking.com, Center Parcs, Coloseum, eDreams, Finnair, LTG Link, MÁV, Pretix, RegioJet, Thalys и United Airlines;</li>
          <li>Correctly update currency exchange rates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Atualizar corretamente as taxas de câmbio.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Корректное обновление курсов валют;</li>
          <li>Add support for result paging for LTG Link and Srbija Voz.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado suporte para paginação de resultados para LTG Link e Srbija Voz.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка постраничного просмотра результатов для LTG Link и Srbija Voz;</li>
          <li>Support hotel reservations with ticket tokens.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para reservas de hotéis com vouchers de ingressos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка бронирования отелей с билетными токенами;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.08.0" date="2025-08-14">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Train and bus trips can now also be added entirely manually.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agora também é possível adicionar viagens de trem e ônibus de forma totalmente manual.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поездки на поезде и автобусе теперь можно добавлять полностью вручную;</li>
          <li>More flexible alternative connection search.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Busca de conexões alternativas mais flexível.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Более гибкий поиск альтернативных соединений;</li>
          <li>New and much more detailed public transport departures view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova visualização das partidas de transporte público, muito mais detalhada.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый и гораздо более подробный просмотр отправлений общественного транспорта;</li>
          <li>Improved location search.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Busca de localização aprimorada.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшенный поиск местоположений;</li>
          <li>OpenRailwayMap integration in the live status view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração do OpenRailwayMap na visualização de status em tempo real.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Интеграция с OpenRailwayMap в представлении текущего статуса;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.04.3" date="2025-07-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Amadeus, booking.com, Deutsche Bahn, Deutscher Alpenverein, DJH, Easyjet, Eurostar, Eurowings, Hostelling Scotland, Leo Express, LeShuttle, MÁV, Ouigo ES, Reenio, SNCB, SNCF, Tickets.ua and Tito.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Amadeus, booking.com, Deutsche Bahn, Deutscher Alpenverein, DJH, Easyjet, Eurostar, Eurowings, Hostelling Scotland, Leo Express, LeShuttle, MÁV, Ouigo ES, Reenio, SNCB, SNCF, Tickets.ua e Tito.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули для извлечения данных о путешествиях для Amadeus, booking.com, Deutsche Bahn, Deutscher Alpenverein, DJH, Easyjet, Eurostar, Eurowings, Hostelling Scotland, Leo Express, LeShuttle, MÁV, Ouigo ES, Reenio, SNCB, SNCF, Tickets.ua и Tito;</li>
          <li>Expanded public transport coverage via Transitous in India, Israel, Korea, Kosovo, Monaco, Macedonia, Moldova and Romania.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ampliação da cobertura de transporte público via Transitous na Índia, Israel, Coreia, Kosovo, Mônaco, Macedônia, Moldávia e Romênia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Расширено покрытие общественного транспорта через Transitous в Индии, Израиле, Корее, Косово, Монако, Македонии, Молдове и Румынии;</li>
          <li>Fixed importing and displaying certain types of Apple Wallet passes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na importação e exibição de certos tipos de passes do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено импортирование и отображение определённых типов пропусков Apple Wallet;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.04.2" date="2025-06-05">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for booking.com, Eurostar, Flixbus, IHG, Stena Line, Tallink and Viking Line.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para booking.com, Eurostar, Flixbus, IHG, Stena Line, Tallink e Viking Line.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые и улучшенные модули для извлечения документов о путешествиях для booking.com, Eurostar, Flixbus, IHG, Stena Line, Tallink и Viking Line;</li>
          <li>Improved automatic public transport backend selection when crossing coverage borders.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na seleção automática do sistema de transporte público ao cruzar fronteiras de cobertura.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшен автоматический выбор источника данных общественного транспорта при пересечении границ покрытия;</li>
          <li>Added onboard API support for Ouigo ES.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada compatibilidade com a API integrada do Ouigo ES.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка бортового API для Ouigo ES;</li>
          <li>Fixed arrival platform parsing from OpenTripPlanner backends.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na análise da plataforma de chegada a partir dos sistemas internos do OpenTripPlanner.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен анализ платформы прибытия из серверов OpenTripPlanner;</li>
          <li>Fixed train direction display on vehicle layout page.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da direção do trem na página de layout do veículo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение направления поезда на странице схемы вагонов;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.04.1" date="2025-05-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for a&amp;o hostels, Gastronovi and ÖBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para a&amp;o hostels, Gastronovi e ÖBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные анализаторы документов путешествий для a&amp;o hostels, Gastronovi и ÖBB;</li>
          <li>Improved geocoding in the address editor.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Geocodificação aprimorada no editor de endereços.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено геокодирование в редакторе адресов;</li>
          <li>Fix trip groups getting split up when updating multi-ticket reservations.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema que fazia com que os grupos de viagem fossem divididos ao atualizar reservas com vários bilhetes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена проблема разделения групп поездок при обновлении бронирований с несколькими билетами;</li>
          <li>Fix displaying city names in Transitous stop search results.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema de exibição dos nomes das cidades nos resultados de pesquisa de paradas de trânsito.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение названий городов в результатах поиска остановок Transitous;</li>
          <li>Fix ÖBB onboard API support.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do suporte à API integrada da ÖBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена поддержка бортового API ÖBB;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="25.04.0" date="2025-04-17">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New timeline layout and new public transport search result view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Novo layout de linha do tempo e nova visualização dos resultados de busca em transporte público.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новое оформление временной шкалы и новый вид результатов поиска общественного транспорта;</li>
          <li>New "My Data" page.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova página "Meus Dados".</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новая страница «Мои данные»;</li>
          <li>Support imperial distance and temperature units.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte a unidades imperiais de distância e temperatura.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка имперских единиц расстояния и температуры;</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractor for Amtrak, Booking.com, Color Line, Eventbrite, Eventlook, Kolumbus ferries, Preemly, SNCF, Tootoot, UIC FCB v3, UK rail, Universe and VDV eTickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Amtrak, Booking.com, Color Line, Eventbrite, Eventlook, Kolumbus Ferries, Preemly, SNCF, Tootoot, UIC FCB v3, UK Rail, Universe e VDV eTickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули для извлечения данных для документов путешествий Amtrak, Booking.com, Color Line, Eventbrite, Eventlook, паромов Kolumbus, Preemly, SNCF, Tootoot, UIC FCB v3, железных дорог Великобритании, Universe и электронных билетов VDV;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.12.3" date="2025-03-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Eventyay, Flixbus, Ghotel, SBB, SNCF and VR.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Eventyay, Flixbus, Ghotel, SBB, SNCF e VR.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые и улучшенные модули извлечения данных из документов для Eventyay, Flixbus, Ghotel, SBB, SNCF и VR;</li>
          <li>Don't hide essential trip group map elements on low zoom levels.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Não ocultar elementos essenciais do mapa do grupo de viagem em níveis de zoom baixos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Основные элементы карты группы поездок не скрываются при малых масштабах;</li>
          <li>Fix data corruption when live data updates would change the type of a reservation.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da corrupção de dados quando atualizações de dados em tempo real alterarem o tipo de reserva.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена ошибка повреждения данных при изменении типа бронирования в результате обновления актуальных данных;</li>
          <li>Disable no longer available DB online import.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Desativar a importação online de banco de dados que não está mais disponível.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Отключён более недоступный онлайн-импорт DB;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.12.2" date="2025-02-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New and improved travel document extractors for American Airlines, Bilkom, Booking.com, CitizenM, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Flixbus, KD, Koleo, Lufthansa, PKP, Polregio, SBB, Southwest, Universe.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos e aprimorados para American Airlines, Bilkom, Booking.com, CitizenM, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Flixbus, KD, Koleo, Lufthansa, PKP, Polregio, SBB, Southwest e Universe.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые и улучшенные модули для извлечения данных из документов American Airlines, Bilkom, Booking.com, CitizenM, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Flixbus, KD, Koleo, Lufthansa, PKP, Polregio, SBB, Southwest, Universe;</li>
          <li>Fix public transport access for Deutsche Bahn (Germany), Digitransit (Finnland), Entur (Norway) and Rolph (Germany).</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do acesso ao transporte público para Deutsche Bahn (Alemanha), Digitransit (Finlândia), Entur (Noruega) e Rolph (Alemanha).</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен доступ к общественному транспорту для Deutsche Bahn (Германия), Digitransit (Финляндия), Entur (Норвегия) и Rolph (Германия);</li>
          <li>Allow transfers to favorite location independent of the next reservation.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir traslados para locais favoritos independentemente da próxima reserva.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Разрешены трансферы в избранное место независимо от следующего бронирования;</li>
          <li>Fix importing passes or other things without an attached trip group.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema na importação de passes ou outros itens sem um grupo de viagem associado.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено импортирование пропусков и других элементов без привязанной группы поездки;</li>
          <li>Fix deleting generic pkpass passes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema de exclusão de passes PKPass genéricos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено удаление обычных билетов pkpass;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.12.1" date="2025-01-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow to add transfers in more cases.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir a adição de transferências em mais casos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность добавления пересадок в большем количестве случаев;</li>
          <li>Fix adding daylight saving time info elements in single trip group mode.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema que adiciona elementos de informação sobre o horário de verão no modo de grupo de viagens individuais.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено добавление элементов информации о летнем времени в режиме одной группы поездок;</li>
          <li>Ignore cancelled elements when determining weather forecast length.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ignorar os elementos cancelados ao determinar a duração da previsão do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Игнорирование отменённых элементов при определении длительности прогноза погоды;</li>
          <li>Override instead of merge destination names when applying new journeys.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ao aplicar novas viagens, substitui os nomes de destino em vez de os mesclar.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Переопределение имён пунктов назначения вместо объединения при применении новых маршрутов;</li>
          <li>Fix crash on importing health certificates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema que causava falha na importação de certificados de saúde.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено падение при импорте справок о здоровье;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.12.0" date="2024-12-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New per-trip timeline view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova visualização da linha do tempo por viagem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новое представление временной шкалы для каждой поездки;</li>
          <li xml:lang="uk">Новий режим перегляд розкладу для кожної з подорожей</li>
          <li>New trip map view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova visualização do mapa da viagem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый вид карты маршрута;</li>
          <li>New per-trip statistics.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Novas estatísticas por viagem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новая статистика по поездкам;</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractor for Coloseum, Dimedis Fairmate, Droplabs, European Sleeper, Flixbus, Leo Express, SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Coloseum, Dimedis Fairmate, Droplabs, European Sleeper, Flixbus, Leo Express e SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый или улучшенный модуль извлечения данных из билетов для Coloseum, Dimedis Fairmate, Droplabs, European Sleeper, Flixbus, Leo Express, SNCF;</li>
          <li>Improved location search for public transport searches.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Busca de localização aprimorada para transporte público.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшен поиск местоположений для поиска общественного транспорта;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.08.3" date="2024-11-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractor for Agoda, Booking.com, NS, planway.com, Renfe, VietJet Air and Thai state railways.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Agoda, Booking.com, NS, planway.com, Renfe, VietJet Air e ferrovias estatais tailandesas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый или улучшенный модуль для извлечения данных о путешествиях для Agoda, Booking.com, NS, planway.com, Renfe, VietJet Air и Государственных железных дорог Таиланда;</li>
          <li>Added support for NS onboard API.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado suporte para a API integrada do NS.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка бортового API NS;</li>
          <li>Fixed display of disrupted/canceled journeys.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da exibição de trechos interrompidos/cancelados.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение нарушенных и отменённых поездок;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.08.2" date="2024-10-10">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed mixed up translations on Android with a multi-language configuration.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correções de traduções misturadas no Android com configuração multilíngue.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена путаница с переводами на Android при многоязычной конфигурации;</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Eurostar, Eventim, Koleo, NH Hotels, Trenitalia and SBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Eurostar, Eventim, Koleo, NH Hotels, Trenitalia e SBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные процедуры извлечения данных из документов для Eurostar, Eventim, Koleo, NH Hotels, Trenitalia и SBB;</li>
          <li>Extended public transport coverage via Transitous.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Ampliação da cobertura de transporte público via Transitous.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Расширенное покрытие общественного транспорта через Transitous;</li>
          <li>Fix importing from overly long URLs.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema na importação de URLs excessivamente longas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен импорт из слишком длинных URL;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.08.1" date="2024-09-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for BlablaBus, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Italo, MAV, Reisnordland ferries, Reservix, Sunnycars, United Airlines and VDV e-tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para BlablaBus, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Italo, MAV, balsas Reisnordland, Reservix, Sunnycars, United Airlines e bilhetes eletrônicos VDV.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули для извлечения данных о путешествиях для BlablaBus, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Italo, MAV, паромов Reisnordland, Reservix, Sunnycars, United Airlines и электронных билетов VDV;</li>
          <li>Fix access to public transport data in Zurich, Switzerland.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do acesso aos dados de transporte público em Zurique, Suíça.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен доступ к данным общественного транспорта в Цюрихе, Швейцария;</li>
          <li>Fix country combo box not opening correctly on phones.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema com a abertura incorreta da caixa de combinação de países em celulares.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено некорректное открытие списка стран на телефонах;</li>
          <li>Dark mode support on Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte ao modo escuro no Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка тёмного режима в Android;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.08.0" date="2024-08-22">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Booking.com, direct-book.com, Entur, Flixbus, MAV, Scandlines, SNCB and SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Booking.com, direct-book.com, Entur, Flixbus, MAV, Scandlines, SNCB e SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые и улучшенные способы извлечения данных из документов для Booking.com, direct-book.com, Entur, Flixbus, MAV, Scandlines, SNCB и SNCF;</li>
          <li>New display for seat reservation information in the timeline.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova exibição das informações de reserva de assentos na linha do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новое отображение информации о бронировании мест в хронологии;</li>
          <li>Support for the Träwelling check-in service.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para o serviço de check-in do Träwelling.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка сервиса регистрации Träwelling;</li>
          <li>Allow to create events or hotel reservations from OSM element URLs.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir a criação de eventos ou reservas de hotel a partir de URLs de elementos do OSM.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность создавать события или бронирования отелей из URL-адресов элементов OSM;</li>
          <li>Allow to show additional Wikimedia online content in the indoor map.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir a exibição de conteúdo online adicional da Wikimedia no mapa interno.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность отображения дополнительного онлайн-контента Wikimedia на планах помещений;</li>
          <li>Trips can now be renamed.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agora é possível renomear as viagens.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поездки теперь можно переименовывать;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.05.2" date="2024-07-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for 12go, Eurowings, hotels.com, Iberia, Georgian Railway, RegioJet, Snälltåget, TCDD and tobilet.pl.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para 12go, Eurowings, hotels.com, Iberia, Georgian Railway, RegioJet, Snälltåget, TCDD e tobilet.pl.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые и улучшенные модули извлечения данных для 12go, Eurowings, hotels.com, Iberia, Georgian Railway, RegioJet, Snälltåget, TCDD и tobilet.pl;</li>
          <li>Fix reading/writing of all-day events to/from the Android system calendar.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema de leitura/gravação de eventos de dia inteiro no/do calendário do sistema Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено чтение и запись событий на весь день в системный календарь Android;</li>
          <li>Fix permission issues when exporting to the Android calendar.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção de problemas de permissão ao exportar para o calendário do Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены проблемы с разрешениями при экспорте в календарь Android;</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apples Wallet passes without a barcode.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema na renderização de passes do Apple Wallet sem código de barras.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение пропусков Apple Wallet без штрихкода;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.05.1" date="2024-06-13">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Air Asia, Amadeus, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Flixbus, Trenitalia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Air Asia, Amadeus, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Flixbus e Trenitalia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных из документов для путешествий Air Asia, Amadeus, Deutsche Bahn, Eurostar, Flixbus, Trenitalia;</li>
          <li>Fixed storing the arrival time when editing a ferry reservation.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema que impedia o armazenamento do horário de chegada ao editar uma reserva de balsa.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено сохранение времени прибытия при редактировании бронирования парома;</li>
          <li>Fixed notifications on Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Notificações corrigidas no Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены уведомления в Android;</li>
          <li>Improved automatic trip grouping.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agrupamento automático de viagens aprimorado.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшена автоматическая группировка поездок;</li>
          <li>Fixed emojis not showing up in Flatpaks.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema que impedia a exibição de emojis em arquivos Flatpak.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение эмодзи в Flatpak;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for CFR, Eurostar, Indico, IRCTC, Lufthansa, Motel One, SNCB, SNCF, Ticketportal, Trenitalia and VDV eTickets. Added support for public transport data from Serbijavoz and Transitous.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para CFR, Eurostar, Indico, IRCTC, Lufthansa, Motel One, SNCB, SNCF, Ticketportal, Trenitalia e VDV eTickets. Adicionado suporte para dados de transporte público da Serbijavoz e Transitous.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые и улучшенные модули извлечения данных из документов для CFR, Eurostar, Indico, IRCTC, Lufthansa, Motel One, SNCB, SNCF, Ticketportal, Trenitalia и VDV eTickets. Добавлена поддержка данных общественного транспорта от Serbijavoz и Transitous;</li>
          <li>Show more detailed train coach or vehicle feature information.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir informações mais detalhadas sobre as características dos vagões ou veículos do trem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Показать подробную информацию о вагоне поезда или характеристиках транспортного средства.</li>
          <li>Show per-coach occupancy information when available.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir informações sobre a ocupação por vagão, quando disponíveis.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Показывать информацию о заполненности по вагонам при её наличии;</li>
          <li>Allow to manually add ticket barcodes to existing reservations.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir a adição manual de códigos de barras de bilhetes a reservas existentes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность вручную добавлять штрихкоды билетов к существующим бронированиям;</li>
          <li>Show DST transition information in the timeline.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir informações sobre a transição para o horário de verão na linha do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Показывать информацию о переходе на летнее время в ленте событий;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Amsbus.cz, Eurostar, Finnair, Moongate, UK national railway and VR.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Amsbus.cz, Eurostar, Finnair, Moongate, ferrovias nacionais do Reino Unido e VR.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные процедуры извлечения данных о проездных документах для Amsbus.cz, Eurostar, Finnair, Moongate, UK national railway и VR;</li>
          <li>Fix displaying public transport departure disruptions.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema na exibição de interrupções nos horários de partida do transporte público.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение сбоев в отправлении общественного транспорта;</li>
          <li>Fix Apple Wallet pass rendering issues.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção dos problemas de renderização de passes do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены проблемы с отображением пропусков Apple Wallet;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Deutsche Bahn, Eckerö Line, European Sleeper, Eventim, Flibco, Leo Express, National Express, ÖBB, osmcal.org, Salzbergwerk, SNCF and ti.to.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Deutsche Bahn, Eckerö Line, European Sleeper, Eventim, Flibco, Leo Express, National Express, ÖBB, osmcal.org, Salzbergwerk, SNCF e ti.to.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные процедуры извлечения данных из проездных документов для Deutsche Bahn, Eckerö Line, European Sleeper, Eventim, Flibco, Leo Express, National Express, ÖBB, osmcal.org, Salzbergwerk, SNCF и ti.to.</li>
          <li>Filter implausible geo coder results on address editing.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Filtrar resultados implausíveis do geocodificador na edição de endereços.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Фильтрация неправдоподобных результатов геокодирования при редактировании адреса;</li>
          <li>Fix overlap between floating map button and arrival details on the journey details page.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da sobreposição entre o botão flutuante do mapa e os detalhes de chegada na página de detalhes da viagem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено наложение плавающей кнопки карты и данных о прибытии на странице сведений о поездке;</li>
          <li>Improve Deutsche Bahn realtime information when facing cancelled or replacement trains.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhorar as informações em tempo real da Deutsche Bahn em caso de cancelamento ou substituição de trens.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшена информация Deutsche Bahn в реальном времени при отменённых или заменяющих поездах;</li>
          <li>Improve train coach type detection in the coach layout view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria da detecção do tipo de vagão de trem na visualização do layout dos vagões.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено определение типа вагона в представлении схемы вагонов.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28">
      <url>https://kde.org/announcements/megarelease/6/#itinerary</url>
      <description>
        <p>We improved the usability of Itinerary on phones by making common actions available on a bottom navigation bar which makes it easy to switch to your passes and your current trip.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoramos a usabilidade do Itinerary em celulares, disponibilizando ações comuns em uma barra de navegação inferior, o que facilita a alternância entre seus passes e sua viagem atual.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Улучшена удобство использования Itinerary на телефонах: часто используемые действия вынесены на нижнюю панель навигации, что упрощает переключение между проездными документами и текущей поездкой.</p>
        <p>The main timeline was redesigned and now entries can be expanded inline to show the intermediate stops and ongoing delays and disruptions. Speaking of events, it is now possible to manually add and edit entries and to share entire trips or single reservations to your phone via KDE Connect.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">A linha do tempo principal foi redesenhada e agora as entradas podem ser expandidas diretamente na página para mostrar as paradas intermediárias, atrasos e interrupções em andamento. Falando em eventos, agora é possível adicionar e editar entradas manualmente, além de compartilhar viagens inteiras ou reservas individuais com seu celular através do KDE Connect.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">Главная временная шкала была переработана: теперь записи можно разворачивать для отображения промежуточных остановок, текущих задержек и сбоев. Также появилась возможность добавлять и редактировать записи вручную, а также передавать целые поездки или отдельные бронирования на телефон через KDE Connect.</p>
        <p>The indoor map in Itinerary now lists all amenities in the building or area you are currently looking at. This helps with things like finding a place to grab a coffee in a big train station, or searching for a place to get food in the vicinity of your hotel. This feature is powered by OpenStreetMap, works without the need to connect to the internet and no search terms ever leave your device.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O mapa interno do Itinerary agora lista todas as comodidades do edifício ou área que você está visualizando. Isso ajuda a encontrar, por exemplo, um lugar para tomar um café em uma grande estação de trem ou um restaurante perto do seu hotel. Esse recurso é fornecido pelo OpenStreetMap, funciona sem a necessidade de conexão com a internet e nenhum termo de pesquisa sai do seu dispositivo.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">На карте помещений в Itinerary теперь отображаются все удобства в здании или районе, который вы сейчас просматриваете. Это помогает, например, найти место, где можно взять кофе на большой железнодорожной станции, или найти место, где можно поесть рядом с вашим отелем. Эта функция работает на основе данных OpenStreetMap, не требует подключения к интернету, и никакие поисковые запросы никогда не покидают ваше устройство.</p>
        <p>When viewing a trip details, in addition to being able to consult the list of stops, it can look at a map of the trip.</p>
        <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Ao visualizar os detalhes de uma viagem, além de poder consultar a lista de paradas, também é possível ver um mapa da viagem.</p>
        <p xml:lang="ru">При просмотре деталей поездки, помимо возможности просмотра списка остановок, доступен просмотр карты маршрута</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="23.08.4" date="2023-12-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for 12go, Eurostar, Flixbus, Motel One, SAS and Thalys.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para 12go, Eurostar, Flixbus, Motel One, SAS e Thalys.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных для 12go, Eurostar, Flixbus, Motel One, SAS и Thalys;</li>
          <li>Improved support for European FCB railway ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria no suporte para códigos de barras de bilhetes ferroviários FCB europeus.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшена поддержка штрихкодов на железнодорожных билетах FCB в Европе;</li>
          <li>Support for Eurostar onboard API.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para a API de bordo do Eurostar.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка бортового API Eurostar;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix handling of canceled intermediate stops on board of DB ICEs.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do tratamento de paradas intermediárias canceladas a bordo de trens de passageiros de grande porte da DB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена обработка отменённых промежуточных остановок в поездах DB ICE;</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for booking.com, DB, European Sleeper, Iberia, PKP, Pretix, Qatar Airways.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para booking.com, DB, European Sleeper, Iberia, PKP, Pretix e Qatar Airways.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных о проездных документах для booking.com, DB, European Sleeper, Iberia, PKP, Pretix, Qatar Airways;</li>
          <li>Fix parsing certain invalid Apple Wallet message catalogs.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema na análise de determinados catálogos de mensagens inválidos do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен анализ синтаксиса некоторых некорректных каталогов сообщений Apple Wallet;</li>
          <li>Remove unnecessary PDF fonts to reduce the APK size.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Remoção das fontes PDF desnecessárias para reduzir o tamanho do APK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Удаление ненужных шрифтов PDF для уменьшения размера APK;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow to enable notifications on Android 13.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir a ativação de notificações no Android 13.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность включения уведомлений в Android 13;</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aegean, Amadeus, bookingkit, GWR, Pretix, Renfe, ÖBB and UK railway tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para bilhetes ferroviários da Aegean, Amadeus, BookingKit, GWR, Pretix, Renfe, ÖBB e do Reino Unido.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных для проездных документов Aegean, Amadeus, bookingkit, GWR, Pretix, Renfe, ÖBB и железнодорожных билетов Великобритании;</li>
          <li>Render more amenity details on the train station map.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir mais detalhes sobre as comodidades no mapa da estação de trem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Отображение дополнительных сведений об удобствах на карте вокзала;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aer Lingus, Amtrak, British Airways, Deutsche Bahn, GVH, premiumkino, Slovak Lines and ZSSK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Aer Lingus, Amtrak, British Airways, Deutsche Bahn, GVH, premiumkino, Slovak Lines e ZSSK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных для проездных документов Aer Lingus, Amtrak, British Airways, Deutsche Bahn, GVH, premiumkino, Slovak Lines и ZSSK;</li>
          <li>Fix editing bus and train elements without an associated ticket.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema na edição de elementos de ônibus e trem sem um bilhete associado.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено редактирование элементов автобусов и поездов без связанного билета;</li>
          <li>Fix unnecessarily broad permissions on Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção das permissões excessivamente amplas no Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены излишне широкие разрешения в Android;</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet generic pass thumbnail images.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema na renderização das miniaturas genéricas de passes do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение миниатюрных изображений универсальных пропусков Apple Wallet;</li>
          <li>Fix progress display on the initial journey stopover in the live status view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da exibição do progresso na parada inicial da viagem na visualização de status ao vivo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение прогресса на начальной остановке маршрута в представлении текущего статуса;</li>
          <li>Display luggage lockers, lost &amp; found offices and ariport baggage claim belts on the indoor map.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir no mapa interno os guarda-volumes, os serviços de achados &amp; perdidos e as esteiras de bagagem dos aeroportos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Отображение камер хранения, бюро находок и лент выдачи багажа в аэропортах на схеме помещений;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Preferred transport modes can now selected for all public transport searches.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agora é possível selecionar os meios de transporte preferenciais para todas as buscas por transporte público.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможно выбрать предпочитаемые виды транспорта для всех поисков общественного транспорта.</li>
          <li>Public transport line logos are now also available for some regional and long distance rail services.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Os logotipos das linhas de transporte público agora também estão disponíveis para alguns serviços ferroviários regionais e de longa distância.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Логотипы линий общественного транспорта теперь также доступны для некоторых региональных и междугородных железнодорожных перевозок;</li>
          <li>Added support for railway coach layouts for more types of trains.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado suporte para layouts de vagões ferroviários para mais tipos de trens.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка схем вагонов для большего числа типов поездов;</li>
          <li>Added support for importing Deutsche Bahn and SNCF online tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada a possibilidade de importar bilhetes online da Deutsche Bahn e da SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка импорта электронных билетов Deutsche Bahn и SNCF;</li>
          <li>Added location sharing via Matrix.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado o compartilhamento de localização através do Matrix.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлен обмен местоположением через Matrix;</li>
          <li>Consider coach layout and seat reservation data to highlight the departure/arrival spot on a platform.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Considera o layout do vagão e os dados de reserva de assentos para destacar o local de partida/chegada em uma plataforma.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Теперь учитывается расположение вагонов и данные о бронировании мест для выделения места отправления/прибытия на платформе;</li>
          <li>New look for the timeline entries and the editing pages.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Novo visual para as entradas da linha do tempo e para as páginas de edição.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новое оформление записей на временной шкале и страниц редактирования.</li>
          <li>New or improved onboard API support for Aegean Air, Deutsche Bahn and ÖBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Novo suporte ou melhorias na API de bordo para Aegean Air, Deutsche Bahn e ÖBB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена или улучшена поддержка бортового API для Aegean Air, Deutsche Bahn и ÖBB;</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aegean Air, Aer Lingus, Air Asia, Air France, Atlatos, Bäder Suite, BlaBlaCar, bookingkit, CD, Cinemaxx, Cooltix, DSB, Eventbrite, FerriesInGreece, Grimaldi Lines, Iberia, KLM, Koleje Malopolskie, KTEL Thesprotias, Lufthansa, Ouigo Spain, PKP, UK railways, SAS, SBB, Slovak Lines, SNCB, spiritec, Spring Airlines, Sunny Cars, Thalys, Trenitalia, York Kino and ZSSK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Aegean Air, Aer Lingus, Air Asia, Air France, Atlatos, Bäder Suite, BlaBlaCar, bookingkit, CD, Cinemaxx, Cooltix, DSB, Eventbrite, FerriesInGreece, Grimaldi Lines, Iberia, KLM, Koleje Malopolskie, KTEL Thesprotias, Lufthansa, Ouigo Spain, PKP, UK railways, SAS, SBB, Slovak Lines, SNCB, spiritec, Spring Airlines, Sunny Cars, Thalys, Trenitalia, York Kino e ZSSK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных о проездных документах для Aegean Air, Aer Lingus, Air Asia, Air France, Atlatos, Bäder Suite, BlaBlaCar, bookingkit, CD, Cinemaxx, Cooltix, DSB, Eventbrite, FerriesInGreece, Grimaldi Lines, Iberia, KLM, Koleje Malopolskie, KTEL Thesprotias, Lufthansa, Ouigo Spain, PKP, UK railways, SAS, SBB, Slovak Lines, SNCB, spiritec, Spring Airlines, Sunny Cars, Thalys, Trenitalia, York Kino и ZSSK.</li>
          <li>Added support for importing ActivityPub events.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada a possibilidade de importar eventos do ActivityPub.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка импорта событий ActivityPub;</li>
          <li>Added support for editing many more reservation and ticket details.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada a possibilidade de editar muito mais detalhes de reservas e bilhetes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена возможность редактирования многих других деталей бронирования и билетов;</li>
          <li>Documents can now be attached to all tickets and reservations, and are automatically attached in more cases.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agora é possível anexar documentos a todos os bilhetes e reservas, e eles são anexados automaticamente em mais casos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">К билетам и бронированиям теперь возможно прикреплять документы; в большинстве случаев они прикрепляются автоматически;</li>
          <li>New hotel, event and restaurant reservation can be created by adding a URL to their schema.org annotated website.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">É possível criar novas reservas de hotel, eventos e restaurantes adicionando uma URL ao site anotado com schema.org.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые бронирования отелей, мероприятий и ресторанов создаются добавлением URL-адреса их веб-сайта с аннотациями schema.org;</li>
          <li>Added support for extracting travel data in Apple iCal events.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada a possibilidade de extrair dados de viagens em eventos do Apple iCal.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлена поддержка извлечения данных о поездках из событий Apple iCal;</li>
          <li>Improved notifications in case of Apple Wallet pass updates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Notificações aprimoradas em caso de atualizações de passe do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшены уведомления при обновлении пропусков Apple Wallet;</li>
          <li>Improved display of ticket validity times in the passes and programs view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na exibição dos horários de validade dos ingressos na visualização de passes e programas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено отображение времени действия билетов в представлении пропусков и программ;</li>
          <li>Improved display of public transport cancellations and long disruption notes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na visualização de cancelamentos e avisos de interrupções prolongadas no transporte público.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено отображение отмен рейсов общественного транспорта и длинных уведомлений о сбоях;</li>
          <li>Fixed searching for international railway connections sometimes not finding any result.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema em que a busca por conexões ferroviárias internacionais às vezes não retornava nenhum resultado.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен поиск международных железнодорожных соединений, который иногда не находил результатов;</li>
          <li>Fixed weather icons sometimes wrongly using the night variants during the day.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema em que os ícones meteorológicos, por vezes, utilizavam incorretamente as variantes noturnas durante o dia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены значки погоды, иногда неправильно использующие ночные варианты в течение дня;</li>
          <li>Fixed too rapid realtime data update queries in case of network errors.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da rapidez excessiva das consultas de atualização de dados em tempo real em caso de erros de rede.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены слишком частые запросы на обновление данных в реальном времени при сетевых ошибках;</li>
          <li>Fixed exported events not being editable by other calendaring apps on Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema que impedia a edição de eventos exportados por outros aplicativos de calendário no Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена невозможность редактирования экспортированных событий другими приложениями календаря в Android;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Color Line, DJH, Fjord Line, Flixbus, Grimladi Lines, onepagebooking, SNCB, Thalys and Trenitalia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Color Line, DJH, Fjord Line, Flixbus, Grimaldi Lines, onepagebooking, SNCF, Thalys e Trenitalia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных для Color Line, DJH, Fjord Line, Flixbus, Grimladi Lines, onepagebooking, SNCB, Thalys и Trenitalia;</li>
          <li>Fixed a crash on Android when importing a file with a space in its path.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido um erro que causava o fechamento inesperado do aplicativo no Android ao importar um arquivo com um espaço no caminho.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено аварийное завершение на Android при импорте файла с пробелом в пути;</li>
          <li>Fixed public transport queries for VRS.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Consultas sobre transporte público corrigidas para VRS.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены запросы к общественному транспорту для VRS;</li>
          <li>Fixed missing transport mode information for some OpenTripPlanner results.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigida a falta de informações sobre o modo de transporte em alguns resultados do OpenTripPlanner.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отсутствие информации о виде транспорта для некоторых результатов OpenTripPlanner;</li>
          <li>Filter implausible walking paths from public transport routers.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Filtra trajetos a pé implausíveis a partir de rotas de transporte público.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исключение неправдоподобных пешеходных маршрутов из результатов маршрутизации общественного транспорта;</li>
          <li>Fixed importing boat or ferry reservations from the calendar.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na importação de reservas de barcos ou balsas a partir do calendário.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен импорт бронирования лодок или паромов из календаря.</li>
          <li>Fixed an infinite loop when computing indoor map arguments.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido um loop infinito no cálculo dos argumentos do mapa interno.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен бесконечный цикл при вычислении аргументов для карт помещений.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed automatic transfer selection producing nonsense when geo coordinates are missing.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema na seleção automática de transferência que gerava erros quando faltavam coordenadas geográficas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен выбор автоматической пересадки, который приводил к бессмыслице при отсутствии географических координат.</li>
          <li>Fixed showing of attached Appled Wallet passes for trains, hotels, busses and car rental reservations.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na exibição dos passes da Apple Wallet anexados a reservas de trem, hotel, ônibus e aluguel de carros.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение прикреплённых пропусков Apple Wallet для поездов, отелей, автобусов и бронирований проката автомобилей.</li>
          <li>Fixed a potential deadlock on updating currency conversion rates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido um possível impasse na atualização das taxas de conversão de moeda.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена возможная взаимная блокировка при обновлении курсов валют.</li>
          <li>Fixed attaching documents to multi-traveler reservations.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção no problema de anexação de documentos a reservas com múltiplos viajantes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено присоединение документов к бронированиям для нескольких путешественников.</li>
          <li>Improved scrolling speed of the timeline view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Velocidade de rolagem da visualização da linha do tempo aprimorada.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшена скорость прокрутки представления временной шкалы.</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for European Sleeper, IndiGo, PKP, Qatar Airways, SBB, SNCB, Thalys as well as for Latvian and Lithuanian railway tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para European Sleeper, IndiGo, PKP, Qatar Airways, SBB, SNCB, Thalys, bem como para bilhetes ferroviários da Letônia e da Lituânia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные процедуры извлечения данных из проездных документов для European Sleeper, IndiGo, PKP, Qatar Airways, SBB, SNCB, Thalys, а также для латвийских и литовских железнодорожных билетов.</li>
          <li>New generic ERA FCB ticket barcode extractor.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Novo extrator genérico de código de barras para ingressos ERA FCB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый универсальный модуль для извлечения данных из штрихкодов билетов ERA FCB.</li>
          <li>Improved extractor for restaurant data in websites.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extrator aprimorado para dados de restaurantes em sites.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшен модуль извлечения данных о ресторанах с веб-сайтов.</li>
          <li>Fixed merging of public transport disruption notes from different sources.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da mesclagem das informações sobre interrupções no transporte público provenientes de diferentes fontes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено объединение уведомлений о сбоях в работе общественного транспорта из разных источников.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved travel document extractors for Air Asia, ATPI, B&amp;B Hotels, Best Western, CD, FlixBus, Gepard Express, Grimaldi Lines, MAV, SNCB and Vueling.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem aprimorados para Air Asia, ATPI, B&amp;B Hotels, Best Western, CD, FlixBus, Gepard Express, Grimaldi Lines, MAV, SNCB e Vueling.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшены модули извлечения данных из проездных документов для Air Asia, ATPI, B&amp;B Hotels, Best Western, CD, FlixBus, Gepard Express, Grimaldi Lines, MAV, SNCB и Vueling.</li>
          <li>Support importing various variants of the Deutschlandticket.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para importação de diversas variantes do Deutschlandticket.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка импорта различных вариантов Deutschlandticket;</li>
          <li>Fixed rendering of MAV ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na renderização dos códigos de barras dos bilhetes MAV.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен вывод штрихкодов билетов MAV.</li>
          <li>Fixed public transport queries in the Czech Republic and the UK.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da consultas sobre transporte público na República Tcheca e no Reino Unido.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены запросы к расписанию общественного транспорта в Чехии и Великобритании;</li>
          <li>Fixed imported PDFs losing their file name on Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema em que PDFs importados perdiam o nome do arquivo no Android.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена потеря имени файла импортированных PDF-файлов в Android.</li>
          <li>Improved Apple Wallet boarding pass layout for overflowing labels.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Layout aprimorado do cartão de embarque do Apple Wallet para etiquetas que excedem o tamanho permitido.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено оформление посадочных талонов Apple Wallet для переполненных меток.</li>
          <li>Improved handling of canceled elements in the timeline.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria no tratamento de elementos cancelados na linha do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшена обработка отменённых элементов на временной шкале;</li>
          <li>Improved rendering of barrier elements in the train station map.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na renderização dos elementos de barreira no mapa da estação de trem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено отображение элементов барьеров на карте вокзала;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aegean Air, Amadeus, availpro, BlaBlaCar, Deutsche Bahn, Kinoheld, Meetup, National Express, ÖBB, Octorate, Ouigo, Premier Inn, SNCF, Taiwan Highspeed Rail and whyline.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem novos ou aprimorados para Aegean Air, Amadeus, availpro, BlaBlaCar, Deutsche Bahn, Kinoheld, Meetup, National Express, ÖBB, Octorate, Ouigo, Premier Inn, SNCF, Taiwan Highspeed Rail e whyline.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули извлечения данных о проездных документах для Aegean Air, Amadeus, availpro, BlaBlaCar, Deutsche Bahn, Kinoheld, Meetup, National Express, ÖBB, Octorate, Ouigo, Premier Inn, SNCF, Taiwan Highspeed Rail и whyline;</li>
          <li>Support for Eurostar, SBB and UK railway ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para códigos de barras de bilhetes da Eurostar, SBB e ferrovias do Reino Unido.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка штрихкодов на билетах Eurostar, SBB и железных дорог Великобритании;</li>
          <li>New live status page using onboard vehicle API.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova página de status em tempo real usando a API integrada do veículo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новая страница текущего состояния с использованием бортового API транспортного средства;</li>
          <li>New UI for reservation details pages.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova interface de usuário para páginas de detalhes de reservas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый интерфейс для страниц сведений о бронировании;</li>
          <li>Faster loading of train station and airport maps.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Carregamento mais rápido de mapas de estações de trem e aeroportos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Ускорена загрузка карт вокзалов и аэропортов;</li>
          <li>Improved display of doors, trees, barrier blocks, platform section markers and accessibility information on train station maps.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na visualização de portas, árvores, cancelas, marcadores de seção da plataforma e informações de acessibilidade nos mapas da estação de trem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено отображение дверей, деревьев, блоков ограждений, маркеров секций платформ и информации о доступности на картах вокзалов;</li>
          <li>Allow to enable LED light for barcode scanning.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir a ativação da luz LED para leitura de código de barras.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность включить светодиодную подсветку для сканирования штрихкода;</li>
          <li>Fix wrong public transport service being used in France.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do serviço de transporte público incorreto que está sendo utilizado na França.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен неправильный выбор общественного транспорта во Франции;</li>
          <li>Fix public transport data access in Switzerland.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do acesso a dados de transporte público na Suíça.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен доступ к данным общественного транспорта в Швейцарии;</li>
          <li>Fix handling of pasted URLs.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do tratamento de URLs coladas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена обработка вставленных URL-адресов;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.3" date="2023-03-02">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved data extraction for Flixbus and UK railway tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração de dados aprimorada para bilhetes da Flixbus e de trens do Reino Unido.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено извлечение данных для билетов Flixbus и железных дорог Великобритании;</li>
          <li>Fixed eliding of stop names in the journey view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema de omissão dos nomes das paradas na visualização da viagem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено обрезание названий остановок в представлении поездки;</li>
          <li>Fixed missing timezone display for times in UTC.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema de ausência na exibição do fuso horário para horários em UTC.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отсутствие отображения часового пояса для времени в формате UTC;</li>
          <li>Fixed train station map stacking order for layered building parts.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da ordem de empilhamento do mapa da estação de trem para partes de edifícios em camadas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен порядок наложения карт железнодорожных станций для многоуровневых частей зданий;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.2" date="2023-02-02">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved data extraction for booking.com, Deutsche Bahn, Indico, MÁV, onepagebooking and Pretix.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração de dados aprimorada para booking.com, Deutsche Bahn, Indico, MÁV, onepagebooking e Pretix.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено извлечение данных для booking.com, Deutsche Bahn, Indico, MÁV, onepagebooking и Pretix;</li>
          <li>Improved merging of separate train ticket and seat reservation data.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na integração de dados separados de bilhetes de trem e reservas de assentos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено объединение данных отдельных билетов на поезд и бронирования мест;</li>
          <li>Fixed rendering of certain Apple Wallet event tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção na renderização de alguns ingressos de eventos do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение некоторых билетов на мероприятия из Apple Wallet;</li>
          <li>Fixed importing multiple generic Apple Wallet passes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema na importação de vários passes genéricos do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен импорт нескольких общих пропусков Apple Wallet;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.1" date="2023-01-05">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support importing of Mobilizon events.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte à importação de eventos do Mobilizon.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка импорта событий Mobilizon;</li>
          <li>Improved travel data extraction for Eventim, MÁV, NH Hotels, Trenitalia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração de dados de viagens aprimorada para Eventim, MÁV, NH Hotels, Trenitalia.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено извлечение данных о поездках для Eventim, MÁV, NH Hotels, Trenitalia;</li>
          <li>Fix display of floating rental vehicles.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da exibição de veículos de aluguel flutuantes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение арендованных транспортных средств;</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet event passes with background images.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema na renderização dos passes de evento do Apple Wallet com imagens de fundo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение пропусков на мероприятия Apple Wallet с фоновыми изображениями;</li>
          <li>Improve map gesture interaction on favorite location picker.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria da interação por gestos no seletor de locais favoritos do mapa.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено взаимодействие с картой с помощью жестов при выборе избранных мест;</li>
          <li>Fix interaction with near-horizontal or near-vertical stairs on the train station map.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da interação com escadas quase horizontais ou quase verticais no mapa da estação de trem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено взаимодействие с почти горизонтальными или почти вертикальными лестницами на схеме вокзала;</li>
          <li>Fix handling of always closed opening hours.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do tratamento dos horários de funcionamento sempre fechados.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена обработка постоянно закрытых часов работы;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.0" date="2022-12-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for boat/ferry reservations.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para reservas de barcos/ferries.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка бронирования паромов и лодок;</li>
          <li>Support for ICAO VDS vaccination certificates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para certificados de vacinação VDS da ICAO.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка сертификатов вакцинации ICAO VDS;</li>
          <li>Improved floor level switching for staircases in station/airport maps.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na alternância de níveis de piso para escadas em mapas de estações/aeroportos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено переключение уровней этажей для лестниц на картах вокзалов и аэропортов;</li>
          <li>Stacking order and hit detection fixes for the station/airport maps.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correções na ordem de empilhamento e na detecção de colisões nos mapas de estações/aeroportos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправления порядка наложения и обнаружения касаний для карт станций и аэропортов;</li>
          <li>Fix driving side informations for people living in left-driving countries.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção das informações sobre a direção para pessoas que vivem em países onde se dirige pela esquerda.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена информация о стороне движения для жителей стран с левосторонним движением;</li>
          <li>Fix date/time input for manual train/bus journey searches.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da entrada de data/hora para buscas manuais de viagens de trem/ônibus.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен ввод даты и времени для ручного поиска поездов и автобусов;</li>
          <li>Fix Railjet trains having no coach layout inside Germany.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema com trens Railjet que não possuem configuração de vagões dentro da Alemanha.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отсутствие схемы вагонов у поездов Railjet в Германии;</li>
          <li>Support for ERA FCB ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para códigos de barras de ingressos ERA FCB.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка штрихкодов билетов ERA FCB;</li>
          <li>Various travel document extractor additions and improvements.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Diversas adições e melhorias ao extrator de documentos de viagem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлены и улучшены различные модули для извлечения данных из проездных документов;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.3" date="2022-11-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New travel data extractor for Italo train tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Novo extrator de dados de viagem para bilhetes de trem da Italo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новый модуль извлечения данных для билетов на поезда Italo;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.2" date="2022-10-13">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved travel data extraction for Airbnb, Amadeus, BlaBlaCar, Eventim, Ryanair, SNCF, Thalys, Vueling.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração de dados de viagens aprimorada para Airbnb, Amadeus, BlaBlaCar, Eventim, Ryanair, SNCF, Thalys e Vueling.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено извлечение данных о поездках для Airbnb, Amadeus, BlaBlaCar, Eventim, Ryanair, SNCF, Thalys, Vueling;</li>
          <li>Handle transliteration when comparing traveler names.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Lidar com a transliteração ao comparar nomes de viajantes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Обработка транслитерации при сравнении имён путешественников;</li>
          <li>Fix trip grouping when connecting journey is part of a different reservation.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do agrupamento de viagens quando a conexão entre as viagens faz parte de uma reserva diferente.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено группирование поездок, когда соединяющий маршрут является частью другой брони;</li>
          <li>Fix selecting the right Apple Wallet event ticket for multi-attendee events.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da seleção do ingresso correto do Apple Wallet para eventos com vários participantes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен выбор правильного билета на мероприятие в Apple Wallet для событий с несколькими участниками;</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet event tickets.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema na renderização dos ingressos para eventos da Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение билетов на мероприятия Apple Wallet;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.1" date="2022-09-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improve size and positioning of map overlays.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria do tamanho e o posicionamento das sobreposições de mapa.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшены размер и расположение наложений карты;</li>
          <li>Improved travel data extractors for Amtrak, Flixbus and Vistara.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de dados de viagem aprimorados para Amtrak, Flixbus e Vistara.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшены модули извлечения данных о поездках для Amtrak, Flixbus и Vistara;</li>
          <li>Improved airport terminal and gate detection.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Detecção aprimorada de terminais e portões de embarque em aeroportos.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено определение терминала аэропорта и выхода на посадку;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.0" date="2022-08-18">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved calendar import, allowing more fine-grained selection and supporting Linux too.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importação de calendário aprimorada, permitindo uma seleção mais detalhada e também compatível com Linux.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшен импорт календаря: добавлена возможность более точного выбора и поддержка Linux;</li>
          <li>Support for exporting reservations to the calendar.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para exportação de reservas para o calendário.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка экспорта бронирований в календарь;</li>
          <li>Support for passes and program cards that aren't tied to a specific trip, such as flat-rate or time interval tickets or discount program memberships.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para passes e cartões de programas que não estão vinculados a uma viagem específica, como bilhetes com tarifa fixa ou com intervalo de tempo, ou ainda adesões a programas de desconto.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка пропусков и карт программ, не привязанных к конкретной поездке, например, билетов с фиксированной ставкой или интервальных билетов, а также членства в дисконтных программах;</li>
          <li>Support for adding train and bus trips from online journey searches.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para adicionar viagens de trem e ônibus a partir de buscas online.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность добавления поездок на поезде и автобусе из результатов онлайн-поиска маршрутов;</li>
          <li>Integrated barcode scanner.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Leitor de código de barras integrado.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Встроенный сканер штрихкодов;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix monorail platforms being misdetected as regular railway.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema das plataformas de monotrilho serem erroneamente identificadas como linhas férreas convencionais.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено ошибочное определение платформ монорельса как обычных железнодорожных;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved travel data extraction for Thalys, UK national rail, Eurowings and Eventbrite.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração de dados de viagens aprimorada para Thalys, National Rail do Reino Unido, Eurowings e Eventbrite.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшено извлечение данных о поездках для Thalys, UK national rail, Eurowings и Eventbrite;</li>
          <li>Fixed train load information parsing for German public transport operators.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da análise de informações sobre a carga dos trens para operadores de transporte público alemães.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлен анализ информации о загрузке поездов для немецких операторов общественного транспорта;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.1" date="2022-05-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix the wrong country being displayed in formatted addresses.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do problema que exibe o país errado nos endereços formatados.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено отображение неверной страны в форматированных адресах;</li>
          <li>Display all supported barcode types in Apple Wallet passes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir todos os tipos de código de barras compatíveis nos passes do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Отображение всех поддерживаемых типов штрихкодов в пропусках Apple Wallet;</li>
          <li>Improved travel document extractors for booking.com, Eurowings, onepagebooking.com and SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores de documentos de viagem aprimorados para booking.com, Eurowings, onepagebooking.com e SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Улучшены модули извлечения данных о проездных документах для booking.com, Eurowings, onepagebooking.com и SNCF;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for overnight train coaches in the train coach layout view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para vagões de trem noturnos na visualização do layout dos vagões.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка спальных вагонов в представлении схемы вагонов поезда;</li>
          <li>Show currencies and optionally current conversion rates when entering a different country.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir as moedas e, opcionalmente, as taxas de conversão atuais ao inserir um país diferente.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Отображение валют и, возможно, текущих курсов обмена при въезде в другую страну;</li>
          <li>Allow to add train trips from an online journey query to the timeline.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Permitir adicionar viagens de trem a partir de uma consulta de viagens online à linha do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Возможность добавления поездок на поезде из онлайн-запроса маршрута на временную шкалу;</li>
          <li>New or improved extractors for Renfe, SNCF, ÖBB, Spring Airlines, Peach Aviation.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extratores novos ou aprimorados para Renfe, SNCF, ÖBB, Spring Airlines e Peach Aviation.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Новые или улучшенные модули для извлечения данных из Renfe, SNCF, ÖBB, Spring Airlines, Peach Aviation;</li>
          <li>Highlight severe weather conditions in the weather forecast.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Destaca as condições climáticas severas na previsão do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Выделение неблагоприятных погодных условий в прогнозе погоды;</li>
          <li>Show public holidays in the timeline.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir feriados nacionais na linha do tempo.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Вывод государственных праздников на временной шкале;</li>
          <li>Fixed high DPI scaling issues in the train coach view.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigidos problemas de dimensionamento em alta resolução (DPI) na visualização da cabine do trem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены проблемы с масштабированием на экранах с высоким DPI в представлении вагона поезда;</li>
          <li>Support for Amtrak and IATA train station identifiers.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para identificadores de estações ferroviárias da Amtrak e da IATA.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка идентификаторов станций Amtrak и IATA;</li>
          <li>Support for importing Danish COVID certificates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para importação de certificados dinamarqueses de COVID.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка импорта датских сертификатов о вакцинации от COVID-19;</li>
          <li>Follow system settings on Linux for which external map application to use.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Siga as configurações do sistema Linux para determinar qual aplicativo de mapas externo usar.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">При работе в Linux, теперь используется внешнее картографическое приложение в соответствии с системными настройками;</li>
          <li>Add jump list action to directly open the current ticket.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionar ação à lista de atalhos para abrir diretamente o tíquete atual.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавить действие в список переходов для прямого открытия текущего билета;</li>
          <li>Fixed geometry reassembly issues in the train station map.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigidos problemas de remontagem geométrica no mapa da estação de trem.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлены проблемы со сборкой геометрии на карте железнодорожной станции;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.3" date="2022-03-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add travel data extraction from Air France ticket PDF documents.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionada extração de dados de viagem a partir de documentos PDF de bilhetes da Air France.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Добавлено извлечение данных о поездках из PDF-документов с билетами Air France;</li>
          <li>Fix locale-aware formatting of numbers.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigida a formatação de números de acordo com a localização.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлено форматирование чисел с учётом локали;</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.2" date="2022-02-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix trip grouping producing wrong results in densely populated areas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o agrupamento de viagens que estava gerando resultados incorretos em áreas densamente povoadas.</li>
          <li xml:lang="ru">Исправлена группировка поездок, дававшая неверные результаты в густонаселённых районах;</li>
          <li>Improve vector barcode detection in PDF documents.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria da detecção de códigos de barras vetoriais em documentos PDF.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.1" date="2022-01-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix station map positioning for elements without live data.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o posicionamento no mapa da estação para elementos sem dados em tempo real.</li>
          <li>Improved travel document extraction for Amtrak and VIA Rail.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração aprimorada de documentos de viagem para Amtrak e VIA Rail.</li>
          <li>Support for alternative Hafas platform formats.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte para formatos alternativos da plataforma Hafas.</li>
          <li>Improved opening hours evaluation in the station maps.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na avaliação dos horários de funcionamento nos mapas das estações.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.0" date="2021-12-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New health certificate user interface.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova interface de usuário para certificado de saúde.</li>
          <li>New navigation maneuver details page for individual transport or walking journey sections.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Nova página com detalhes das manobras de navegação para trechos individuais de transporte ou deslocamento a pé.</li>
          <li>Smarter transfer auto-selection.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Seleção automática de transferências mais inteligente.</li>
          <li>Live disruption information and journey details for bus trips.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Informações em tempo real sobre interrupções e detalhes de viagens de ônibus.</li>
          <li>Ability to shorten train and bus trips.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Possibilidade de encurtar viagens de trem e ônibus.</li>
          <li>Additional individual transport modes for transfers.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modalidades adicionais de transporte individual para traslados.</li>
          <li>Improved platform identification for trams and subways.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na identificação das plataformas de bondes e metrôs.</li>
          <li>Easier accessible barcode scan mode, and support for PDF417 ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modo de leitura de código de barras mais acessível e suporte para códigos de barras de bilhetes PDF417.</li>
          <li>Improved data import feedback.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria no feedback da importação de dados.</li>
          <li>Fixed pinch zoom on station maps.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção do zoom com gestos de pinça nos mapas das estações.</li>
          <li>Improved Apple Wallet pass rendering.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhoria na renderização do passe do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li>Warn about rental vehicles with limited remaining range.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Alerta sobre veículos de aluguel com autonomia limitada.</li>
          <li>Numerous improvements to travel document data extraction.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Inúmeras melhorias na extração de dados de documentos de viagem.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.3" date="2021-11-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix icon size issues on high DPI screens.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção de problemas de tamanho de ícones em telas de alto DPI.</li>
          <li>Fix map panning leaving the favorite location selector page.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema de deslocamento do mapa ao sair da página de seleção de locais favoritos.</li>
          <li>Fix determining departure country for location changes.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da determinação do país de partida para alterações de localização.</li>
          <li>Fix erroneous merging of train trips with the same line on the same day.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da mesclagem incorreta de viagens de trem da mesma linha no mesmo dia.</li>
          <li>Fix parsing of OTP rental vehicle information.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Correção da análise das informações de aluguel de veículos com código OTP.</li>
          <li>Apply timezone information correctly to flight reservations with incomplete time information.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Aplicar corretamente as informações de fuso horário às reservas de voo com informações de horário incompletas.</li>
          <li>Improved data extraction for various providers.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração de dados aprimorada para diversos fornecedores.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.2" date="2021-10-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add support for SMART Health Card (SHC) vaccination certificates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Adicionado suporte para certificados de vacinação do SMART Health Card (SHC).</li>
          <li>Don't trigger the connection warning when there is no previous arrival time.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Não aciona o aviso de conexão quando não houver um horário de chegada anterior.</li>
          <li>Show correct number of attached documents for multi-traveller trips.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Apresenta o número correto de documentos anexados para viagens com vários viajantes.</li>
          <li>Show escalators to/from intermediate floor levels correctly in the indoor map. </li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibir corretamente as escadas rolantes de/para os andares intermediários no mapa interno.</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet pass rich-text back fields.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Corrigido o problema na renderização dos campos de texto formatado do Apple Wallet.</li>
          <li>Improved data extraction for SNCF, Accor, Feratel and onepagebooking.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração de dados aprimorada para SNCF, Accor, Feratel e onepagebooking.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.1" date="2021-09-02">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Properly import mail attachments shared from FairEmail.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importa corretamente os anexos de e-mail compartilhados do FairEmail.</li>
          <li>Improvements for importing data from Airdo, MÁV, Regionado, Ryanair and SNCF.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Melhorias na importação de dados da Airdo, MÁV, Regionado, Ryanair e SNCF.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.0" date="2021-08-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Health certificate manager for DIVOC and EU DGC vaccination, test and recovery certificates.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Gestor de certificados de saúde para os certificados de vacinação, teste e recuperação DIVOC e DGC da UE.</li>
          <li>GPX import and export of favorite locations and GPX export of trips for Nextcloud Maps interoperability.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Importação e exportação de GPX de locais favoritos e exportação de GPX de viagens para interoperabilidade com o Nextcloud Maps.</li>
          <li>Support for local German public transport operators INVG, RSAG, VRT and VSN.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporte às empresas de transporte público locais alemãs INVG, RSAG, VRT e VSN.</li>
          <li>Improved travel document extractor.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extrator de documentos de viagem aprimorado.</li>
          <li>Various fixes to the page flow.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Diversas correções no fluxo da página.</li>
          <li>Entire trip groups can now be deleted.</li>
          <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Agora é possível excluir grupos de viagens inteiros.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::f_droid">https://community.kde.org/Android/FDroid#KDE_F-Droid_Release_Repository</value>
    <value key="KDE::google_play">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.kde.itinerary</value>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#itinerary:kde.org</value>
  </custom>
  <branding>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="light">#cdecfc</color>
    <color type="primary" scheme_preference="dark">#17529b</color>
  </branding>
  <recommends>
    <control>keyboard</control>
    <control>pointing</control>
    <control>touch</control>
  </recommends>
  <requires>
    <display_length compare="ge">360</display_length>
  </requires>
</component>
