<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.itinerary</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <name>KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KDE itineraar</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Adde a KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDE 여행 정보</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDE Itinerár</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Itineraryxx</name>
  <summary>Digital travel assistant</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Assistent de viatges digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Assistent de viatges digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Digital travel assistant</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Asistente digital para viajes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Digitaalne reisimise abivahend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Assistance de voyage numérique</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Asistente de viaxes dixital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Asisten travel digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Assistente digitale per i viaggi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">디지털 여행 도우미</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Digitale reisassistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Cyfrowy pomocnik podróży</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Assistente de viagens digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Assistente de viagens digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Digitálny cestovný asistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Digitalt resehjälpprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Цифровий помічник у подорожах</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDigital travel assistantxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Itinerary is a digital travel assistant with a priority on protecting your privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Itinerary és un assistent digital de viatge amb la prioritat de protegir la vostra privadesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KDE Itinerary és un assistent digital de viatge amb la prioritat de protegir la vostra privadesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary es un asistente de viajes digital que tiene como prioridad proteger su privacidad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KDE Itineraar on digitaalne reisiabiline, mis seab sihiks sinu privaatsuse kaitsmise.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary è un assistente di viaggio digitale con una priorità sulla protezionedella tua riservatezza.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary is een digitale reisassistent met prioriteit op beschermen van uw privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Itinerary é um assistente digital de viagens com a prioridade de proteger a sua privacidade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan är ett digitalt resehjälpprogram som prioriterar att skydda din integritet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary — цифровий помічник у подорожах, акцент у якому зроблено на забезпеченні вашої конфіденційності.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Itinerary is a digital travel assistant with a priority on protecting your privacy.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Timeline view of a unified travel itinerary with automatic trip grouping.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista de la línia de temps d'un itinerari unificat de viatges amb agrupació automàtica de viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la línia de temps d'un itinerari unificat de viatges amb agrupació automàtica de viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista cronológica de un itinerario de viaje unificado con agrupación de viajes automática.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ühendatud reisikava ajateljevaade ühes võimalusega reise automaatselt rühmitada.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione della sequenza temporale di un itinerario di viaggio unificato con raggruppamento automatico dei viaggi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Tijdlijn weergave van een geünificeerd reisroute met automatische groepering van trips.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Visão cronológica de um itinerário de viagens unificado com o agrupamento automático das viagens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">TIdslinjevisning av en enhetlig resplan med automatisk resegruppering.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу уніфікованого маршруту подорожі із автоматичним групуванням за поїздками.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTimeline view of a unified travel itinerary with automatic trip grouping.xx</li>
      <li>Supports train, bus and flight bookings as well as hotel, restaurant, event and rental car reservations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet reserva de tren, autobús i avió, així com reserves d'hotels, restaurants, esdeveniments i lloguer de cotxes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rongide, busside ja lennukite ning hotellide, restoranide, sündmuste ja rendiautode broneeringud ja reserveeringud.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt boekingen van trein, bus en vlucht evenals reserveringen van hotel, restaurant, evenement en huurauto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta as reservas de comboios, autocarros e voos, assim como dos hotéis, restaurantes, eventos e alugueres de carros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder tåg-, buss-, och flygbokningar samt bokning av hotell, restauranger, evenemang och hyrbilar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка бронювання квитків на потяги, автобуси та літаки, а також бронювання номерів готелів, місць у ресторанах, участі у подіях та оренди автомобілів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports train, bus and flight bookings as well as hotel, restaurant, event and rental car reservations.xx</li>
      <li>Boarding pass management.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Gestió de les targetes d'embarcament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestió de les targetes d'embarcament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Boarding pass management.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Gestión de tarjetas de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Piletite haldus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion des cartes d'embarquement.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Xestión de pases de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pengelolaan boarding pass.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Gestione delle carte d'imbarco.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">탑승권 관리.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Beheer van boardingpass</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie kartami pokładowymi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gestão de cartões de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciamento de cartões de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Správa leteniek</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hantering av boardingkort.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Керування посадковими квитками.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxBoarding pass management.xx</li>
      <li>Supports ticket management for multi-traveler and multi-ticket bookings.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet la gestió de bitllets per reserves multiviatger i multibitllet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet la gestió de bitllets per reserves multiviatger i multibitllet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite gestión de billetes para reservas de varios viajeros y de varios billetes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Mitme reisija ja mitme pileti reserveerimise piletihalduse toetus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta la gestione dei biglietti per prenotazioni multi-viaggiatore e multi-biglietto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor beheer van tickets voor meerdere reizigers en booking van meerdere tickets.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a gestão de bilhetes para reservas multi-viajantes e multi-bilhetes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder biljetthantering för bokningar med flera resenärer och biljetter.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка керування роботою з квитками для замовлень із пересадками та одночасного замовлення декількох квитків.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports ticket management for multi-traveler and multi-ticket bookings.xx</li>
      <li>Automatic booking data extraction from various input formats, performed locally on your device.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Extracció automàtica de dades de les reserves des de diversos formats d'entrada, efectuades localment en el vostre dispositiu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Extracció automàtica de dades de les reserves des de diversos formats d'entrada, efectuades localment en el vostre dispositiu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Extracción automática de datos de reservas de diversos formatos de entrada, que se realiza localmente en su dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Reserveerimisandmete automaatne hankimine mitmesugustest sisendvormingutest, mis sooritatakse otse sinu seadmes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Estrazione automatica dei dati di prenotazione da vari formati di ingresso, eseguita localmente sul tuo dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Automatische extractie van bookinggegevens ui verschillende invoerformaten, lokaal uitgevoerd op uw apparaat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Extracção automática dos dados da reserva a partir de vários formatos de entrada, operando localmente no seu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Automatisk extrahering av bokningsinformation från diverse indataformat, utförd lokalt på din enhet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичне видобування даних із різноманітних вхідних форматів, яке відбувається безпосередньо на вашому пристрої.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAutomatic booking data extraction from various input formats, performed locally on your device.xx</li>
      <li>Real-time delay and platform change information for trains.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Informació d'endarreriments i canvis de plataforma en temps real per als trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Informació d'endarreriments i canvis de plataforma en temps real per als trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Retrasos e información de cambios de andén en tiempo real para trenes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rongide hilinemise ja platvormivahetuse reaalajas teave.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Informazioni sui ritardi in tempo reale e sui cambi di binario per i treni.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Real-time informatie over vertraging en wijziging van perron voor treinen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Informações em tempo-real de atrasos e mudança de plataformas nos comboios.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Information i realtid om fördröjningar och plattformsändringar för tåg.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інформування про затримки та зміни платформ для потягів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxReal-time delay and platform change information for trains.xx</li>
      <li>Weather forecast for destination along your trip.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Previsió meteorològica de la destinació durant el viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Previsió meteorològica de la destinació durant el viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Previsión meteorológica para el destino a lo largo de su viaje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ilmaennustus kogu reisi kohta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Previsioni meteo per la destinazione lungo il tuo viaggio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Weersvoorspelling voor bestemming langs de reisroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Previsão meteorológica no destino, ao longo da sua viagem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Väderprognos för mål längs resan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Показ прогнозу погоди у кінцевій точці вашої подорожі.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxWeather forecast for destination along your trip.xx</li>
      <li>Full control over all online access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Control total sobre tots els accessos en línia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Control total sobre tots els accessos en línia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Control total sobre todos los accesos con conexión.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Täielik kontroll kogu võrgukasutuse üle.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Pieno controllo su tutti gli accessi in linea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Volledige controle over alle online toegang.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Controlo total sobre todo o acesso 'online'.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständig kontroll över alla nätåtkomster.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Повне керування усіма параметрами доступу до інтернету.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFull control over all online access.xx</li>
      <li>Selection of alternative train connections on unbound tickets or on missed connections.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Selecció de connexions alternatives de tren en bitllets independents o en connexions perdudes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Selecció de connexions alternatives de tren en bitllets independents o en connexions perdudes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Selección de conexiones de tren alternativas en billetes sin consolidar o en conexiones perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Alternatiivse rongiühenduse valimise võimalus näiteks piletite puudumise või mahajäämise korral.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Selezione di collegamenti ferroviari alternativi su biglietti non vincolati o collegamenti persi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Selectie van alternatieve treinverbindingen op niet-gebonden tickets of over gemiste verbindingen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Selecção de ligações de comboio alternativas para bilhetes não vinculados ou para ligações perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Val av alternativa tågförbindelser på öppna biljetter eller vid missade anslutningar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вибір альтернативних залізничних шляхів за умов наявності проїзного або неможливості з'єднання різних частин маршруту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSelection of alternative train connections on unbound tickets or on missed connections.xx</li>
      <li>Local ground transportation navigation between elements of your itinerary.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Navegació de transport local terrestre entre elements de l'itinerari.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Navegació de transport local terrestre entre elements de l'itinerari.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Exploración de transporte terrestre local entre elementos de su itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kohaliku maismaatranspordi kasutamise võimalus reisi etappide vahel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Navigazione del trasporto via terra locale tra gli elementi del tuo itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Lokale navigatie van vervoer op de grond tussen elementen van uw reisroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Navegação local em transportes terrestres entre elementos do seu itinerário.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Navigering för lokal marktransport mellan delar av resplanen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Навігація на місцевості під час пересадок між фрагментами вашого маршруту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLocal ground transportation navigation between elements of your itinerary.xx</li>
      <li>Personal travel statistics to monitor environmental impact.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Estadístiques de viatges personals per controlar l'impacte ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Estadístiques de viatges personals per controlar l'impacte ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Estadísticas de viaje personales para monitorizar el impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Isiklik reisistatistika oma ökoloogilise jalajälje selgitamiseks.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Statistiche di viaggio personali per monitorare l'impatto ambientale.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Persoonlijke reisstatistieken om impact op de omgeving te monitoren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Estatísticas pessoais da viagem para acompanhar o impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Personlig resestatistik för att övervaka miljöpåverkan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Особиста статистика подорожей для стеження за впливом на навколишнє середовище.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPersonal travel statistics to monitor environmental impact.xx</li>
    </ul>
    <p>KDE Itinerary works best alongside KMail's itinerary extraction plug-in and KDE Connect, or Nextcloud Hub and DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Itinerary funciona millor amb el connector d'extracció d'itineraris del KMail i el KDE Connect, o el Nextcloud Hub i el DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KDE Itinerary funciona millor amb el connector d'extracció d'itineraris del KMail i el KDE Connect, o el Nextcloud Hub i el DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary funciona mejor con el complemento de extracción de itinerarios de KMail y con KDE Connect, o con Nextcloud Hub y DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KDE Itineraar töötab kõige paremini koos KMaili reisikava hankimise plugina ja KDE Connectiga või ka Nextcloudi ja DavDroidiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary funziona meglio insieme all'estensione di estrazione degli itinerari di KMail e KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary werkt het best naast de plug-in voor reisroute uitpakken van KMail en KDE Connect of Nextcloud Hub en DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Itinerary funciona melhor com o 'plugin' de extracção de itinerários e com o KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub ou o DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan fungerar bäst tillsammans med Kmails insticksprogram för extrahering av resplan och KDE-anslut, eller Nextcloud-navet och DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary найкраще працює із додатком видобування даних KMail та KDE Connect або Nextcloud Hub і DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Itinerary works best alongside KMail's itinerary extraction plug-in and KDE Connect, or Nextcloud Hub and DavDroid.xx</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Timeline view.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la línia de temps.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la línia de temps.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled časové osy.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Timeline view.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista cronológica.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Ajatelje vaade.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue chronologique.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Vista da liña de tempo.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan linimasa.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista della linea temporale.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">타임라인 보기.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Tijdlijnweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok osi czasu.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista cronológica.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição cronológica.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tidslinjevisning.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTimeline view.xx</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-timeline.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Boarding pass view.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de les targetes d'embarcament.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de les targetes d'embarcament.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de tarjetas de embarque.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Piletivaade.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista delle carte d'imbarco.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Boardingpasweergave.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Visualização do cartão de embarque.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Visning av boardingkort.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд посадкових квитків.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxBoarding pass view.xx</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-boardingpass.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Train layout view highlighting the coach with a seat reservation.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la disposició del tren amb ressaltat del vagó amb una reserva de seient.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Rongi struktuurivaade ühes vaguni ja reserveeritud istme esiletõstmisega.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Treinindelingsweergave met accentuering van het rijtuig met een zitplaats reservering.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Área de disposição dos comboios que realça o lugar com uma reserva.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tågplatsvisning som färglägger vagnen med platsbokning.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Панель місць у вагонах потягу із підсвічуванням заброньованих місць.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTrain layout view highlighting the coach with a seat reservation.xx</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-vehicle-layout.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <url type="homepage">https://community.kde.org/KDE_PIM/KDE_Itinerary</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=KDE+Itinerary</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>itinerary</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.itinerary.desktop</launchable>
</component>
