<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
 SPDX-FileCopyrightText: 2018 Volker Krause <vkrause@kde.org>
 SPDX-License-Identifier: CC0-1.0
-->
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.itinerary</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>LGPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <developer_name translate="no">KDE</developer_name>
  <name>KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Itinerář KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KDE-Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">KDE-Itinero</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KDE itineraar</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Adde a KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KDE 여행 정보</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Маршруты KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KDE Itinerár</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">KDE Yol Kılavuzu</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Itineraryxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Itinerary</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">KDE 旅行計劃</name>
  <summary>Digital travel assistant</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Assistent digital de viatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Assistent digital de viatges</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Digitální asistent na cesty</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Digitaler Reiseassistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Digital travel assistant</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eo">Cifereca vojaĝasistanto</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Asistente digital para viajes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Digitaalne reisimise abivahend</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Bidai-laguntzaile digitala</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Ohjelmallinen matka-avustaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Assistance de voyage numérique</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Asistente de viaxes dixital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">Digitális utazássegéd</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Assistente digital de viage</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Asisten travel digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Assistente digitale per i viaggi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">მოგზაურობის ციფრული დამხმარე</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">디지털 여행 도우미</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Digitale reisassistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Cyfrowy pomocnik podróży</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Assistente de viagens digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Assistente de viagens digital</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Цифровой помощник в путешествиях</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Digitálny cestovný asistent</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Digitalni potovalni pomočnik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Digitalt resehjälpprogram</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sayısal yolculuk asistanı</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Цифровий помічник у подорожах</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDigital travel assistantxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">数字旅行助理应用</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">數位旅行助理</summary>
  <description>
    <p>KDE Itinerary is a digital travel assistant with a priority on protecting your privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Itinerary és un assistent digital de viatges amb la prioritat de protegir la vostra privadesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Itinerary és un assistent digital de viatges amb la prioritat de protegir la vostra privadesa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Itinerář KDE je digitální asistent na cestování jehož prioritou je ochrana vašeho soukromí.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KDE-Itinerary ist ein digitaler Reiseassistent, der den Schutz Ihrer Privatsphäre priorisiert.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Itinerary is a digital travel assistant with a priority on protecting your privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KDE-Itinero estas cifereca vojaĝasistanto kun prioritato pri protektado de via privateco.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary es un asistente de viajes digital que tiene como prioridad proteger su privacidad.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KDE Itineraar on digitaalne reisiabiline, mis seab sihiks sinu privaatsuse kaitsmise.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«KDE Itinerary» bidai-laguntzaile digital bat da, zure pribatutasuna babesteko lehentasuna duena.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KDE Itinerary on ohjelmallinen matka-avustaja, joka ensisijaisesti pyrkii varmistamaan tietoturvasi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDE Itinerary est un assistant de voyage numérique donnant la priorité au respect de votre confidentialité.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KDE Itinerary egy digitális utazássegéd, amelynek kiemelt célja a magánszférájának védelme.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KDE Itinerary es un assistente digital de viage con le prioritate de proteger tu confidentialitate.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KDE Itinerary adalah asisten perjalanan digital dengan prioritas melindungi privasimu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary è un assistente di viaggio digitale con una priorità sulla protezionedella tua riservatezza.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KDE Itinerary მოგზაურობის ციფრული დამხმარეა, თქვენი კონფიდენციალობის შენარჩუნების პრიორიტეტით.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDE 여행 정보는 프라이버시를 지키는 디지털 여행 도우미입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary is een digitale reisassistent met prioriteit op beschermen van uw privacy.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KDE Itinerary jest cyfrowym pomocnikiem podróży, którego nadrzędnym celem jest chronienie twojej prywatności.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Itinerary é um assistente digital de viagens com a prioridade de proteger a sua privacidade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDE Itinerary é um assistente de viagens digital com prioridade na proteção de sua privacidade.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Маршруты KDE — это цифровой помощник в путешествиях, в котором сделан акцент на обеспечении конфиденциальности пользователя.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KDE Itinerary je digitalni pomočnik pri potovanju s pomembno zasnovo pri zaščiti vaše zasebnosti.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan är ett digitalt resehjälpprogram som prioriterar att skydda din integritet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KDE Yol Kılavuzu, gizliliğinize öncelik veren bir sayısal yolculuk asistanıdır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary — цифровий помічник у подорожах, акцент у якому зроблено на забезпеченні вашої конфіденційності.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Itinerary is a digital travel assistant with a priority on protecting your privacy.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Itinerary 是一款注重保护用户隐私的数字旅行助理应用。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">《KDE 旅行計劃》是一個重視保護您的隱私權的數位旅行助理。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ast">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">Trajtoj:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Eginbideak:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuuksia:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Funkciók:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Funzionalità:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">თვისებები:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Mogelijkheden:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">功能：</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Timeline view of a unified travel itinerary with automatic trip grouping.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista de la línia de temps d'un itinerari unificat de viatges amb agrupació automàtica de viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la línia de temps d'un itinerari unificat de viatges amb agrupació automàtica de viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Zeitleistenansicht eines vereinten Reiseplans mit automatischer Reisegruppierung.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Timeline view of a unified travel itinerary with automatic trip grouping.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Templiniovido de unuigita vojaĝa itinero kun aŭtomata vojaĝgrupo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista cronológica de un itinerario de viaje unificado con agrupación de viajes automática.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ühendatud reisikava ajateljevaade ühes võimalusega reise automaatselt rühmitada.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bidai ibilbide bateratu baten denbora-lerro ikuspegia, txango taldekatze automatikoarekin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Yhtenäisen matkasuunnitelman aikajananäkymä matkan automaattisella ryhmittelyllä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Vue chronologique de votre itinéraire de voyage unifié grâce au regroupement automatique des voyages.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Idővonal nézet az egyesített útvonaltervhez, automatikus kiránduláscsoportosítással.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Vista de chronologia de unitinerario unificate viage con gruppamento de viages automatic.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tampilan garis waktu dari rencana perjalanan terpadu dengan pengelompokan perjalanan otomatis.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Visualizzazione della sequenza temporale di un itinerario di viaggio unificato con raggruppamento automatico dei viaggi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">Itinerrary-ის გაერთიანებული მოგზაურობის ხედი დროის ხაზზე, მოვლენების ავტომატური დაჯგუფებით.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">자동 여행 그룹 기능이 있는 통합된 여정 타임라인 보기.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Tijdlijn weergave van een geünificeerd reisroute met automatische groepering van trips.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Widok osi czasu dla ujednoliconego planu podróży z samoczynnym grupowaniem podróży.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Visão cronológica de um itinerário de viagens unificado com o agrupamento automático das viagens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição cronológica de um itinerário de viagem unificado com agrupamento automático de viagem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Просмотр расписания унифицированного маршрута с автоматической группировкой по поездкам.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pogled časovnice poenotenega plana potovanja s samodejnim grupiranjem potovanj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">TIdslinjevisning av en enhetlig resplan med automatisk resegruppering.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Otomatik yolculuk gruplandırması ile birleşik yolcu belgelerinin zaman akışı görünümü.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу уніфікованого маршруту подорожі із автоматичним групуванням за поїздками.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTimeline view of a unified travel itinerary with automatic trip grouping.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">时间线视图，可自动分组并归类旅程。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">整合旅行計劃的時間軸，支援自動為旅程分組。</li>
      <li>Supports train, bus and flight bookings as well as hotel, restaurant, event and rental car reservations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet reserves de tren, autobús i avió, així com reserves d'hotels, restaurants, esdeveniments i lloguer de cotxes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet reserves de tren, autobús i avió, així com reserves d'hotels, restaurants, esdeveniments i lloguer de cotxes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Unterstützung für Zug-, Bus- und Flugbuchungen sowie für Hotel-, Restaurant-, Veranstaltungs- und Mietwagenreservierungen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports train, bus and flight bookings as well as hotel, restaurant, event and rental car reservations.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Subtenas rezervojn de trajno, buso kaj flugo kaj ankaŭ rezervojn de hotelo, restoracio, evento kaj luaŭto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite el uso de reservas de trenes, autobuses y vuelos, así como de hoteles, restaurantes, eventos y alquiler de automóviles.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rongide, busside ja lennukite ning hotellide, restoranide, sündmuste ja rendiautode broneeringud ja reserveeringud.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Tren, autobus eta hegaldi erreserbak onartzen ditu, baita hotel, jatetxe, ekitaldi eta ibilgailu alokairuenak ere.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee juna-, bussi- ja lentolippujen samoin kuin hotellien, ravintoloiden, tapahtumien ja vuokra-autojen varauksia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge des réservations de trains, de bus, de vols, d'hôtels, de restaurants, d'évènements et de véhicules.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Vonat-, busz és repülőjegyek, valamint hotel-, étterem-, eseményfoglalások és autóbérlés támogatása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Supporta reservationes de traino, bus e volo tal como hotel, restaurante, eventos e reservationes de location de vehiculo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Mendukung pemesanan kereta api, bus dan penerbangan serta pemesanan hotel, restoran, acara dan persewaan mobil.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta prenotazioni per treni, autobus e voli aerei così come alberghi, ristoranti, eventi e noleggi auto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აქვს მატარებლის, ავტობუსის და ფრენის ბილეთების დაჯავშნის, ასევე სასტუმროს, რესტორანის, მოვლენისა და მანქანის ქირაობის რეზერვაციების მხარდაჭერა.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">철도, 버스, 항공 예약 이외에도 호텔, 레스토랑, 행사, 렌터카 예약도 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteunt boekingen van trein, bus en vlucht evenals reserveringen van hotel, restaurant, evenement en huurauto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje bilety na pociągi, autobusy i samoloty, a także hotele, restauracje, wydarzenia i wypożyczanie samochodów.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta as reservas de comboios, autocarros e voos, assim como dos hotéis, restaurantes, eventos e alugueres de carros.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporta reservas de trens, ônibus e voos, bem como reservas de hotéis, restaurantes, eventos e aluguel de veículos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка заказа билетов на поезда, автобусы и самолеты, а также бронирования прокатных автомобилей, гостиничных номеров, мест в ресторанах и посещения мероприятий.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira rezervacije vlakov, avtobusov in letal kot tudi hotelov, restavracij, dogodkov in rezervacij najema avtomobilov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder tåg-, buss-, och flygbokningar samt bokning av hotell, restauranger, evenemang och hyrbilar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tren, otobüs ve uçak rezervasyonlarının yanı sıra otel, restoran ve kiralık araç rezervasyonlarını da destekler.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка бронювання квитків на потяги, автобуси та літаки, а також бронювання номерів готелів, місць у ресторанах, участі у подіях та оренди автомобілів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports train, bus and flight bookings as well as hotel, restaurant, event and rental car reservations.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持预订火车、公共汽车、航班、酒店、餐厅、活动和租车服务。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援鐵路、公路與航空訂票，以及飯店、餐廳、活動與租車預約。</li>
      <li>Boarding pass management.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Gestió de les targetes d'embarcament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gestioneu les targetes d'embarcament.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Bordkartenverwaltung.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Boarding pass management.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Administrado de enirpermesiloj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Gestión de tarjetas de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Piletite haldus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Ontziratze-txartelen kudeaketa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Maihinnousukorttien hallinta</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gestion des cartes d'embarquement.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Xestión de pases de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Beszállókártya-kezelés.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Gestion de carta de imbarcar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pengelolaan boarding pass.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Gestione delle carte d'imbarco.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ჩასაჯდომი ბილეთების მართვა.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">탑승권 관리.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Beheer van boardingpass</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zarządzanie kartami pokładowymi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gestão de cartões de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Gerenciamento de cartões de embarque.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Управление посадочными талонами.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Správa leteniek</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Upravljanje vstopnih kuponov.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Hantering av boardingkort.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Biniş kartı yönetimi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Керування посадковими квитками.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxBoarding pass management.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">登机牌管理。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">登機證管理。</li>
      <li>Supports ticket management for multi-traveler and multi-ticket bookings.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Permet la gestió de bitllets per a reserves multiviatger i multibitllet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet la gestió de bitllets per a reserves multiviatger i multibitllet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Fahrkartenverwaltung für Mehrpersonenreisen und Buchungen mit mehreren Fahrkarten.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Supports ticket management for multi-traveller and multi-ticket bookings.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Subtenas biletadministradon por plurvojaĝantoj kaj plurbiletaj rezervoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Permite gestión de billetes para reservas de varios viajeros y de varios billetes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Mitme reisija ja mitme pileti reserveerimise piletihalduse toetus.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bidaiari anizkoitzeko eta txartel anizkoitzeko erreserbetarako txartelak kudeatzeko euskarria du.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tukee useamman matkustajan tai matkalipun varausten lippujen hallintaa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prise en charge de la gestion des billets pour les réservations multi-voyageurs et multi-billets.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Többutasos és többjegyes foglalások jegykezelésének támogatása.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Supporta gestion de billet per reservationes de multi-traveler e multi-ticket.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Mendukung pengelolaan tiket untuk multi-traveller dan pemesanan multi-tiket.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Supporta la gestione dei biglietti per prenotazioni multi-viaggiatore e multi-biglietto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">აქვს მრავალ-მოგზაურიანი და მრავალ-ბილეთიანი ჯავშნების მართვის მხარდაჭერა.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여행자가 여러 명이거나 여러 장의 표로 구성된 예약을 지원합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ondersteuning voor beheer van tickets voor meerdere reizigers en booking van meerdere tickets.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Obsługuje zarządzanie biletami w przypadku rezerwacji u wielu przewoźników i wielu biletów.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Suporta a gestão de bilhetes para reservas multi-viajantes e multi-bilhetes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Suporta o gerenciamento de bilhetes para reservas de vários viajantes e multibancos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поддержка управления работой с билетами для заказа с пересадками и одновременного заказа нескольких билетов.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Podpira upravljanje vozovnic za več potnikov in rezervacij za več vozovnic.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stöder biljetthantering för bokningar med flera resenärer och biljetter.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çok yolculu ve çok biletli rezervasyonlar için bilet yönetimi desteği.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Підтримка керування роботою з квитками для замовлень із пересадками та одночасного замовлення декількох квитків.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSupports ticket management for multi-traveler and multi-ticket bookings.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">支持管理多位旅客的多次订票。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">支援多人與多票券訂票的票券管理。</li>
      <li>Automatic booking data extraction from various input formats, performed locally on your device.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Extracció automàtica de dades de les reserves des de diversos formats d'entrada, efectuades localment en el vostre dispositiu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Extracció automàtica de dades de les reserves des de diversos formats d'entrada, efectuades localment en el vostre dispositiu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Automatische Extraktion von Buchungsdaten aus verschiedenen Eingabeformaten, lokal auf Ihrem Gerät ausgeführt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Automatic booking data extraction from various input formats, performed locally on your device.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Aŭtomata rezervada eltiro de diversaj enigformatoj, farita loke sur via aparato.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Extracción automática de datos de reservas de diversos formatos de entrada, que se realiza localmente en su dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Reserveerimisandmete automaatne hankimine mitmesugustest sisendvormingutest, mis sooritatakse otse sinu seadmes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Hainbat sarrera-formatuetatik erreserba-datuak automatikoki erauztea, zure gailuan bertan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Automaattinen varaustiedon purku useista syötemuodoista paikallisesti omalla laitteellasi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Extraction automatique des données de réservation depuis de nombreux formats d'entrée, réalisée en local sur votre appareil.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Foglalási adatok automatikus kinyerése különböző bemeneti formátumokból, helyben, az Ön eszközén.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Extraction de datos de reservation automatic ex varie formatos de entrata, executate localmente sur tu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Ekstraksi data pemesanan otomatis dari berbagai format input, dilakukan secara lokal di perantimu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Estrazione automatica dei dati di prenotazione da vari formati di ingresso, eseguita localmente sul tuo dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ჯავშნის მონაცემების ავტომატური ამოღება მრავალი ფორმატიდან, რომელიც თქვენს მოწყობილობაზე ხდება.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 입력 자료에서 여정을 추출하며, 로컬 장치에서 이루어집니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Automatische extractie van bookinggegevens ui verschillende invoerformaten, lokaal uitgevoerd op uw apparaat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wydobywanie danych o rezerwacji z różnych formatów wejściowych, wykonywalne lokalnie na twoim urządzeniu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Extracção automática dos dados da reserva a partir de vários formatos de entrada, operando localmente no seu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Extração automática de dados de reserva de vários formatos de entrada, realizada localmente no seu dispositivo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Автоматическое извлечение данных бронирования из различных входных форматов, которое происходит непосредственно на устройстве пользователя.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Avtomatsko pridobivanje podatkov iz različnih vhodnih formatov lokalno v vaši napravi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Automatisk extrahering av bokningsinformation från diverse indataformat, utförd lokalt på din enhet.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yerel olarak aygıtınızda gerçekleştirilen, çeşitli girdi biçimlerinden otomatik rezervasyon verisi çıkarımı.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автоматичне видобування даних із різноманітних вхідних форматів, яке відбувається безпосередньо на вашому пристрої.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAutomatic booking data extraction from various input formats, performed locally on your device.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在设备端处理多种输入格式并自动提取预订数据。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">從多種輸入格式自動取出訂票資料，全部在您的裝置上進行而不會傳送到其他地方。</li>
      <li>Real-time delay and platform change information for trains.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Informació d'endarreriments i canvis d'andana en temps real per als trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Informació d'endarreriments i canvis d'andana en temps real per als trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Echtzeitanzeige von Verspätungen und Gleisänderungen von Zügen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Real-time delay and platform change information for trains.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Realtempa prokrasto kaj platformoŝanĝaj informoj por trajnoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Retrasos e información de cambios de andén en tiempo real para trenes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rongide hilinemise ja platvormivahetuse reaalajas teave.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Trenen atzerapen eta nasa aldaketa informazioa denbora errealean.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Tosiaikainen junien viivästys- ja laiturinmuutostieto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Informations de retard et de changement de quai en temps réel pour les trains.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Valós idejű késés- és vágányinformációk vonatokhoz.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Information de retardo in tempo actual e cambiamento de platteforma per trainos. </li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Informasi penundaan real-time dan perubahan platform untuk kereta api.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Informazioni sui ritardi in tempo reale e sui cambi di binario per i treni.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლების დაყოვნებისა და პლატფორმის ცვლილების რეალურ დროში განახლება.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열차의 실시간 지연 정보와 승강장 변경을 표시합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Real-time informatie over vertraging en wijziging van perron voor treinen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dane w czasie rzeczywistym o opóźnieniach i zmianie peronów dla pociągów.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Informações em tempo-real de atrasos e mudança de plataformas nos comboios.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Atraso em tempo real e informações de mudança de plataforma para trens.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Информация о задержках и изменениях платформ для поездов.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Informacije o zamudah v realnem času in o spremembah peronov za vlake.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Information i realtid om fördröjningar och plattformsändringar för tåg.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Trenler için gerçek zamanlı gecikme ve platform değişikliği bilgisi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Інформування про затримки та зміни платформ для потягів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxReal-time delay and platform change information for trains.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">提供火车延误和站台变更的实时信息。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">火車的即時誤點或月台變更資訊。</li>
      <li>Weather forecast for destination along your trip.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Previsió meteorològica de la destinació durant el viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Previsió meteorològica del destí durant el viatge.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Wettervorhersage für Orte entlang der Reiseroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Weather forecast for destination along your trip.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Veterprognozo por celloko dum via vojaĝo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Previsión meteorológica para el destino a lo largo de su viaje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ilmaennustus kogu reisi kohta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Helmugako eguraldiaren iragarpena bidaiatu bitartean.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kohteen sääennuste matkallesi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Prévisions météorologiques pour la destination tout au long de votre voyage.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Időjárás-előrejelzés a kirándulás útvonalára.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Prevision Meteorologic per destination preter tu viage.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Ramalan cuaca untuk tujuan selama perjalananmu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Previsioni meteo per la destinazione lungo il tuo viaggio.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ამინდის პროგნოზი დანიშნულების პუნქტისაკენ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여행지의 일기 예보를 표시합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Weersvoorspelling voor bestemming langs de reisroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Prognoza pogody dla miejsca docelowego podróży.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Previsão meteorológica no destino, ao longo da sua viagem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Previsão meteorológica para os destinos de sua viagem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Показ прогноза погоды в пункте назначения по ходу путешествия.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vremenska napoved za cilje ob vašem potovanju.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Väderprognos för mål längs resan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yolculuk noktalarınız için hava durumu tahmini.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Показ прогнозу погоди у кінцевій точці вашої подорожі.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxWeather forecast for destination along your trip.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">显示旅途中各个目的地的天气预报。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">旅程上各目的地的天氣預報。</li>
      <li>Full control over all online access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Control total sobre tots els accessos en línia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Control total sobre tots els accessos en línia.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Vollständige Kontrolle über alle Online-Zugriffe.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Full control over all online access.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Plena rego super ĉiu interreta aliro.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Control total sobre todos los accesos con conexión.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Täielik kontroll kogu võrgukasutuse üle.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Lerroko sarbide guzien kontrol osoa.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Täysi hallinta kaikkeen verkkokäyttöön.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Contrôle complet sur tous les accès en ligne.</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">שליטה מלאה בכל הגישה לאינטרנט.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Teljes ellenőrzés minden online hozzáférés felett.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Plen control sur omne accesso in linea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Kontrol penuh atas semua akses online.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Pieno controllo su tutti gli accessi in linea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ონლაინ წვდომის სრული კონტროლი.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">온라인 접근을 완전히 통제합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Volledige controle over alle online toegang.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Pełny nadzór nad dostępem do sieci.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Controlo total sobre todo o acesso 'online'.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Controle completo sobre todos os acessos online.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Полное управление всеми параметрами доступа в Интернет.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Popoln nadzor nad vsemi spletnimi dostopi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Fullständig kontroll över alla nätåtkomster.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tüm çevrimiçi erişim üzerinde tam denetim.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Повне керування усіма параметрами доступу до інтернету.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFull control over all online access.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">完全掌控所有在线功能。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">對於所有線上存取的完整控制。</li>
      <li>Selection of alternative train connections on unbound tickets or on missed connections.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Selecció de connexions alternatives de tren en bitllets independents o en connexions perdudes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Seleccioneu les connexions alternatives de tren en bitllets independents o en connexions perdudes.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Auswahl alternativer Zugverbindungen für Hinreisen oder bei verpassten Verbindungen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Selection of alternative train connections on unbound tickets or on missed connections.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Elekto de alternativaj trajnkonektoj sur nebinditaj biletoj aŭ ĉe sopiritaj konektoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Selección de conexiones de tren alternativas en billetes sin consolidar o en conexiones perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Alternatiivse rongiühenduse valimise võimalus näiteks piletite puudumise või mahajäämise korral.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Loturarik gabeko txarteletan edo galdutako konexioetan ordezko tren-konexioak hautatzea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Vaihtoehtoisten junayhteyksien valinta, jos lippuja ei ole sidottu tai jatkoyhteys menetettiin.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Sélection de correspondances ferroviaires alternatives pour les tickets non liés ou les correspondances manquées.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Alternatív vonatjáratok kiválasztása a nem kötött menetjegyek vagy lekésett csatlakozások esetében.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Selection de connexiones alternative de traino sur billetes libere o sur connexiones mancate.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pemilihan koneksi kereta api alternatif untuk tiket tidak terikat atau koneksi yang terlewat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Selezione di collegamenti ferroviari alternativi su biglietti non vincolati o collegamenti persi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლების სხვა მიერთებების არჩევანის მხარდაჭერა გაუქმებული ბილეთების ან დაგვიანებული გადაჯდომის დროს.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열차를 놓쳤거나 자유 여정 승차권의 경우 대체 열차편 정보를 제공합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Selectie van alternatieve treinverbindingen op niet-gebonden tickets of over gemiste verbindingen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wybór zamiennych połączeń kolejowych dla nieprzypisanych biletów lub przegapionych połączeń.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Selecção de ligações de comboio alternativas para bilhetes não vinculados ou para ligações perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Seleção de conexões ferroviárias alternativas em bilhetes não consolidados ou em conexões perdidas.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Выбор альтернативных железнодорожных маршрутов при наличии проездного илиопоздании на пересадку.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Izbira alternativnih železniških povezav na nevezanih vozovnicah ali vozovnicah zamujenih povezav.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Val av alternativa tågförbindelser på öppna biljetter eller vid missade anslutningar.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Açık biletler veya kaçırılan aktarmalar için alternatif tren önerileri seçimi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вибір альтернативних залізничних шляхів за умов наявності проїзного або неможливості з'єднання різних частин маршруту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSelection of alternative train connections on unbound tickets or on missed connections.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">使用非绑定票券或错过联运交通时改签联运火车。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在使用未限制的票券或是沒趕上轉乘時可選取替代的火車轉乘。</li>
      <li>Local ground transportation navigation between elements of your itinerary.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Navegació de transport local terrestre entre elements de l'itinerari.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Navegació de transport local terrestre entre elements de l'itinerari.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Lokale Navigation mit Bodenverkehr zwischen Abschnitten Ihres Reiseplans.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Local ground transportation navigation between elements of your itinerary.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Loka surtera transporta navigado inter elementoj de via itinero.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Exploración de transporte terrestre local entre elementos de su itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kohaliku maismaatranspordi kasutamise võimalus reisi etappide vahel.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Zure ibilbideko elementuen artean, lurreko tokiko garraioa nabigatzea.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Paikallinen maaliikennenavigointi matkasuunnitelmasi osien välillä.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Navigation à l'aide des transports en commun régionaux entre deux éléments de votre itinéraire.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Helyi földi közlekedési navigáció az útvonal elemei között.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Navigation de transportation de terra local inter elementos de tu itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Navigasi transportasi darat lokal antara elemen rencana perjalananmu.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Navigazione del trasporto via terra locale tra gli elementi del tuo itinerario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">ადგილობრივი სახმელეთო ტრანსპორტირების ნავიგაცია თქვენი მარშრუტის ელემენტებს შორის.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여행 중에 이용할 지역 대중 교통 정보를 제공합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Lokale navigatie van vervoer op de grond tussen elementen van uw reisroute.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Lokalne przemieszczanie się naziemne pomiędzy elementami twojego planu podróży.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Navegação local em transportes terrestres entre elementos do seu itinerário.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Navegação por transporte terrestre local entre elementos do seu itinerário. </li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Навигация по местному наземному транспорту между фрагментами маршрута.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Lokalna navigacija po zemeljskih prevozi med elementi vašega plana potovanja.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Navigering för lokal marktransport mellan delar av resplanen.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Yolcu belgesi ögeleriniz arasında yerel yer ulaşımı dolaşımı.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Навігація на місцевості під час пересадок між фрагментами вашого маршруту.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxLocal ground transportation navigation between elements of your itinerary.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">在各段行程间为您进行本地地面交通导航。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在您的旅行計劃項目之間的本地地面運輸導覽。</li>
      <li>Train coach layout view (for some operators only).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Vista de la disposició de vagons del tren (només per a alguns operadors).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la disposició de vagons del tren (només per a alguns operadors).</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Ansicht der Wagenreihung von Zügen (nur für einige Betreiber).</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Train coach layout view (for some operators only).</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Trajna vagona enpaĝigvido (nur por kelkaj funkciigistoj).</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista del esquema del tren (solo para algunos operadores).</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Tren bagoiaren antolaeraren ikuspegia (operatzaile batzuetan bakarrik).</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Junien vaunukarttanäkymä (joillekin operaattoreille).</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Affichage des compositions des trains (pour certains opérateurs uniquement)</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Vonatalaprajz nézet (csak egyes szolgáltatók esetén).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Vista de disposition de carrossa (solment eper alcun operatores)</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Tampilan tata letak gerbong kereta (hanya untuk beberapa operator).</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Vista della disposizione della carrozza del treno (solo per alcuni operatori).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის ვაგონში ადგილების დათვალიერება (მხოლოდ ზოგიერთი ოპერატორისთვის).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">열차 객차 구성 보기(일부 철도 사업자만).</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Weergave van indeling treinwagons (alleen voor sommige vervoerders)</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Widok układu wagonu kolejowego (tylko dla wybranych przewoźników).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Área de disposição dos lugares do comboio (apenas com alguns operadores).</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização do layout do vagão (somente para alguns operadores).</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Просмотр мест в вагоне поезда (только для некоторых операторов).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pogled postavitve vlaka (samo za nekatere operaterje).</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tågvagnslayout (bara för vissa operatörer).</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tren vagonu yerleşimi görünümü (yalnızca bazı operatörlerde).</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перегляд місць у вагоні потягу (лише для деяких операторів).</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTrain coach layout view (for some operators only).xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">列车编组视图 (仅限某些运营商)。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">檢視火車車廂內部配置（僅部分交通機構）。</li>
      <li>Train station and airport per-floor maps based on OpenStreetMap data.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Mapes per planta de l'estació de tren i l'aeroport basats en les dades d'OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mapes per planta de l'estació de tren i l'aeroport basats en les dades d'OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Geschosskarten von Bahnhöfen und Flughäfen basierend auf OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Train station and airport per-floor maps based on OpenStreetMap data.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Trajna stacidomo kaj flughaveno po-etaĝaj mapoj bazitaj sur OpenStreetMap-datenoj.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Planos de las plantas de estaciones de tren y de aeropuertos basados en datos de OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Tren geltokiko eta aireportuko solairukako mapak, «OpenStreetMap»ako datuetan oinarrituta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">OpenStreetMapin tietoon perustuvat rautatie- ja lentoasemien kerroskartat.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les cartes de gares et d'aéroports s'appuyant sur les données de OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Az OpenStreetMap adatain alapuló, emeletenkénti vasútállomási és repülőtéri térképek.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Mappas per plano de  Station de traino e aeroporto basate sur datos de OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Peta stasiun kereta dan bandara per lantai berdasarkan data OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Mappe per piano di stazioni ferroviarie e aeroporti basate sui dati di OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">რკინიგზის სადგურებისა და აეროპორტების სართულების რუკა OpenStreetMap -ზე დაყრდნობით.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">OpenStreetMap 데이터를 사용하는 기차역과 공항 층별 지도 보기.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Kaarten per verdieping van station en luchthaven gebaseerd op gegevens uit OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Plany pięter dworców kolejowych i lotnisk na podstawie danych z OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Mapas das estações de comboio e aeroportos por pisos, baseados em dados do OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Mapas de estações de trem e aeroportos por andar com base em dados do OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Поэтажные карты железнодорожных станций и аэропортов на основе данных OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zemljevidi železniške postaje in letališča po nadstropjih na podlagi podatkov OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tågstations- och flygplatskartor för varje våning baserade på data från OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">OpenStreetMap verisine dayalı tren istasyonu ve havaalanı kat haritaları.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Мапи поверхів залізничних станцій та аеропортів засновано на даних OpenStreetMap.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTrain station and airport per-floor maps based on OpenStreetMap data.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">基于 OpenStreetMap 数据的火车站地图和机场多层地图。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">基於 OpenStreetMap 資料的火車站與機場各樓層地圖。</li>
      <li>Available dock-based or free-floating rental bikes can be displayed on the train station map.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Les bicicletes de lloguer disponibles ancorades o flotants es poden mostrar en el mapa de l'estació de tren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Les bicicletes de lloguer disponibles ancorades o flotants es poden mostrar en el mapa de l'estació de tren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Anzeige von verfügbaren Leihfahrrädern – sowohl mit als auch ohne Verleihstation – auf Bahnhofskarten.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Available dock-based or free-floating rental bikes can be displayed on the train station map.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Disponeblaj dok-bazitaj aŭ liber-flosantaj lubicikloj povas esti montritaj sur la fervoja stacidoma mapo.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Las bicicletas de alquiler disponibles en base o sin ella se pueden mostrar en el mapa de la estación de tren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Alokairuko bizikleta erabilgarriak, nasa-oinarrikoak edo higikorrak, tren-geltokiko mapan azal daitezke.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Saatavilla olevat vapaat potkulaudat tai vuokrapyörät voidaan näyttää rautatieaseman kartalla.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Les vélos de location disponibles en libre service ou en station d'accueil peuvent être affichés sur la carte des gares. </li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Szabad dokkolós vagy szabadon szállítható kölcsönözhető kerékpárok megjelenítése a vasútállomások térképein.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Bicyclettas disponiile de locar basate sur bassino o libere de flottar pote esser monstrate sur le mapa de station de traino.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Penyewaan sepeda dock-based atau free-floating yang tersedia dapat ditampilkan di peta stasiun kereta.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Le biciclette a noleggio disponibili su rastrelliera o a flusso libero possono essere visualizzate sulla mappa della stazione ferroviaria.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის სადგურის რუკაზე შეგიძლიათ დოკზე ბაზირებული ან თავისუფლად მოსრიალე გაქირავებადი ველოსიპედები გაჩვენოთ.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">기차역 지도에 고정 스테이션에 있거나 고정되어 있지 않은 렌탈 자전거를 표시할 수 있습니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Beschikbare huurfietsen in stalling en vrijstaand kan getoond worden op de kaart van het treinstation.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dostępne rowery do wypożyczenia w systemie ze stacjami lub bez nich, można wyświetlić na mapie dworca kolejowego.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Poderá mostrar as bicicletas de aluguer com bloqueios ou livres no mapa das estações dos correios.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">As bicicletas de aluguel disponíveis em docas ou avulsas podem ser exibidas no mapa da estação de trem.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">На карте железнодорожной станции могут быть показаны доступные прокатныевелосипеды со стационарной или произвольной парковкой.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Razpoložljiva kolesa za najem na stebričkih ali prosto dostopna kolesa na zemljevidu železniške postaje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Tillgängliga stationsbaserade eller fristående hyrcyklar kan visas på tågstationskartan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tren istasyonu haritasında rıhtımlı veya serbest bırakılmış kiralık bisiklet bilgisi görüntülenebilir.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">На мапі залізничної станції може бути показано доступні орендовані велосипеди зі стаціонарними або довільними місцями паркування.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAvailable dock-based or free-floating rental bikes can be displayed on the train station map.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">火车站地图显示空余的有桩或无桩共享单车。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">在火車站地圖上可以顯示可用的腳踏車租借，支援停車柱式或是自由停靠的腳踏車租借。</li>
      <li>Personal travel statistics to monitor environmental impact.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Estadístiques de viatges personals per a controlar l'impacte ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Estadístiques de viatges personals per a controlar l'impacte ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Persönliche Reisestatistik zur Auswertung des Einflusses auf die Umwelt.</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Personal travel statistics to monitor environmental impact.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eo">Personaj vojaĝaj statistikoj por monitori median efikon.</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Estadísticas de viaje personales para monitorizar el impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Isiklik reisistatistika oma ökoloogilise jalajälje selgitamiseks.</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Bidaia pertsonalen estatistikak ingurumen eragina gainbegiratzeko.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Matkan henkilökohtaiset tilastot ympäristövaikutusten tarkkailemiseksi.</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Statistiques de voyages personnels pour calculer l'impact environnemental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="hu">Személyes utazási statisztikák a környezeti hatások nyomon követésére.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Statistica de viage personal a supervisionar impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Statistik perjalanan pribadi untuk memantau dampak lingkungan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Statistiche di viaggio personali per monitorare l'impatto ambientale.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">მოგზაურობის სტატისტიკა გარემოზე ეფექტის მონიტორინგისთვის.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">환경 영향을 계산하는 개인 여행 통계 정보를 제공합니다.</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Persoonlijke reisstatistieken om impact op de omgeving te monitoren.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Osobisty statystyki podróżowania do monitorowania wpływu na środowisko.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Estatísticas pessoais da viagem para acompanhar o impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Estatísticas pessoais da viagem para monitorar o impacto ambiental.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Личная статистика путешествий для наблюдения за воздействием на окружающую среду.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Osebna statistika potovanj za spremljanje vplivov na okolje.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Personlig resestatistik för att övervaka miljöpåverkan.</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çevre etkisini izlemek üzere kişisel yolculuk istatistikleri.</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Особиста статистика подорожей для стеження за впливом на навколишнє середовище.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxPersonal travel statistics to monitor environmental impact.xx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">个人旅行统计数据，可观察您对环境的影响。</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-TW">個人旅行統計資料，讓您追蹤自己的環境影響。</li>
    </ul>
    <p>KDE Itinerary works best alongside KMail's itinerary extraction plug-in and KDE Connect, or Nextcloud Hub and DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KDE Itinerary funciona millor amb el connector d'extracció d'itineraris del KMail i el KDE Connect, o el Nextcloud Hub i el DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">KDE Itinerary funciona millor amb el connector d'extracció d'itineraris de KMail i KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub i DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">KDE-Itinerary funktioniert am besten in Verbindung mit KMails Itinerary-Extraktionsmodulen und KDE Connect, oder mit Nextcloud Hub und DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Itinerary works best alongside KMail's itinerary extraction plug-in and KDE Connect, or Nextcloud Hub and DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eo">KDE-Itinero funkcias plej bone kune kun la aldonaĵo de KMail-eltiro de itinero kaj KDE Connect, aŭ Nextcloud Hub kaj DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KDE Itinerary funciona mejor con el complemento de extracción de itinerarios de KMail y con KDE Connect, o con Nextcloud Hub y DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KDE Itineraar töötab kõige paremini koos KMaili reisikava hankimise plugina ja KDE Connectiga või ka Nextcloudi ja DavDroidiga.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">«KDE Itinerary» hobe dabil «KMail»en ibilbidea erauzteko pluginarekin eta «KDE Connect» edo «Nextcloud Hub» eta «DavDroid»ekin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">KDE Itinerary toimii parhaiten yhdessä KMailin matkasuunnitelmatietoliitännäisen ja KDE Connectin tai Nextcloud Hubin ja DavDroidin kanssa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">KDE Itinerary fonctionne au maximum de ses capacités avec le module d'extraction des itinéraires de KMail et KDEConnect mais aussi avec Nextcloud Hub et DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">A KDE Itinerary a legjobban a KMail itinerkinyerő bővítménye és a KDE Connect vagy a Nextcloud Hub és DavDroid mellett működik.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">KDE Itinerary functiona meliormente  con plugin de extraction de itinerario de KMail e KDE Connect, o Hub de Nextcloud e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KDE Itinerary bekerja paling baik dengan plugin itinerary extraction KMail dan KDE Connect, atau Nextcloud Hub dan DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KDE Itinerary funziona meglio insieme all'estensione di estrazione degli itinerari di KMail e KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">KDE Itinerarary ყველაზე კარგად KMail-ის დამატებასთან, KDE Connect-თან, Nextcloud Hub-თან და DavDroid-თან მუშაობს.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KDE 여행 정보는 KMail의 여행 정보 추천 플러그인, KDE Connect, Nextcloud 허브 및 DavDroid와 같이 작동합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KDE Itinerary werkt het best naast de plug-in voor reisroute uitpakken van KMail en KDE Connect of Nextcloud Hub en DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KDE Itinerary działa najlepiej wraz z wtyczką do wydobywania itinerary dla KMaila oraz KDE Connect, lub Nextcloud Hub i DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KDE Itinerary funciona melhor com o 'plugin' de extracção de itinerários e com o KDE Connect, o Nextcloud Hub ou o DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KDE Itinerary funciona melhor junto com o plugin de extração de itinerário do KMail e KDE Connect ou Nextcloud Hub e DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Программа «Маршруты KDE» лучше всего работает с модулем извлечения маршрутов KMail и KDE Connect или Nextcloud Hub и DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KDE Itinerary deluje najbolje skupaj z dodatki z vtičnikom za ekstrakcijo podatkov v KMail in KDE Connect ali Nextcloud Hub in DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">KDE-resplan fungerar bäst tillsammans med Kmails insticksprogram för extrahering av resplan och KDE-anslut, eller Nextcloud-navet och DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">KDE Yol Kılavuzu, en iyi olarak K Posta’nın yolculuk belgesi çıkarma eklentisi ve KDE Bağlan, Nextcloud Hub veya DavDroid ile birlikte çalışır.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KDE Itinerary найкраще працює із додатком видобування даних KMail та KDE Connect або Nextcloud Hub і DavDroid.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Itinerary works best alongside KMail's itinerary extraction plug-in and KDE Connect, or Nextcloud Hub and DavDroid.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">KDE Itinerary 是 KMail 行程提取插件和 KDE Connect 的最佳搭档，还能配合 Nextcloud Hub 和 DavDroid 使用。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">《KDE 旅行計劃》與 KMail 的旅行計劃取出外掛程式及 KDE 連線，或是 Nextcloud Hub 及 DavDroid 共同使用時更方便。</p>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Timeline view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la línia de temps</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la línia de temps</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled časové osy</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Zeitleistenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Timeline view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Templinio vido</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista cronológica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Denbora-lerro ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Aikajananäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Vue chronologique.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת ציר זמן</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Idővonal nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de Chronologia.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan linimasa</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista della linea temporale</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">დროის ხაზის ხედი</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">타임라인 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Tijdlijnweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok osi czasu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista cronológica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Exibição cronológica</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр расписания</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled časovnice</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tidslinjevisning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Zaman akışı görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд розкладу</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTimeline viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">时间线视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">時間軸檢視</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-timeline.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Boarding pass view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de les targetes d'embarcament</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de les targetes d'embarcament</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled na nástupní doklad</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Bordkartenansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Boarding pass view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Vido de enirado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de tarjetas de embarque</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Ontziratze-txartel ikuspegia.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Maihinnousukorttinäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage de la carte d'embarquement.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת כרטיס עלייה לאמצעי התחבורה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Beszállókártya nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de carta de imbarcar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan boarding pass</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista delle carte d'imbarco</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">თვითმფრინავის ბილეთის ნახვა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">탑승권 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Boardingpasweergave</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok kart odpraw</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Vista do cartão de embarque</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização do cartão de embarque</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр посадочных талонов</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled vstopnega kupona</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Visning av boardingkort</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Biniş kartı görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Перегляд посадкових квитків</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxBoarding pass viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">登机牌视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">登機證檢視</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-boardingpass.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Train layout view highlighting the coach with a seat reservation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de la disposició del tren amb ressaltat del vagó amb una reserva de seient</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de la disposició del tren amb ressaltat del vagó amb una reserva de seient</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Wagenreihungsansicht mit Hervorhebung des Wagens mit Sitzplatzreservierung</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Train layout view highlighting the coach with a seat reservation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Trajna aranĝo vido elstarigante la trejniston kun sidloko rezervado</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista del esquema del tren resaltando el coche con reserva de asiento</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tren antolamenduaren ikuspegia, eserleku-erreserba duen bagoia nabarmenduta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Varatun paikan korostava junan vaunukartta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage de la composition du train, détaillant la voiture où le siège est réservé.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Vonat alaprajza a helyfoglalással rendelkező kocsit kiemelve</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Dispoition de traino evidentiante le carrossa con un reservation de placia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan tata letak kereta yang menyoroti gerbong dengan reservasi kursi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista della disposizione del treno che evidenzia la carrozza con la prenotazione di un posto</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის განლაგების ხედი სავარძლის რეზერვაციის გამოკვეთით</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">예약한 열차 좌석이 강조된 열차 구성 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Treinindelingsweergave met accentuering van het rijtuig met een zitplaats reservering</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok układu pociągu z rezerwacją miejsc</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Área de disposição dos comboios que realça o lugar com uma reserva</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização do layout do trem destacando o vagão com reserva de assento</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр мест в вагонах поезда с подсветкой вагона с забронированным местом</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled postavitve vlaka s poudarjenim vagonom in rezervacijo sedeža</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tågplatsvisning som färglägger vagnen med platsbokning</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Koltuk rezervasyonunu vurgulayan vagon görünümlü tren yerleşimi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Панель місць у вагонах потягу із підсвічуванням заброньованих місць</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTrain layout view highlighting the coach with a seat reservationxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">列车编组视图，高亮显示了车厢中预订的座位</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">火車佈局檢視，突顯座位預約與車廂</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-vehicle-layout.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Train station platform map, highlighting arrival and departure platforms</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Mapa d'andanes de l'estació de tren, destacant les andanes d'arribada i sortida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mapa d'andanes de l'estació de tren, destacant les andanes d'arribada i eixida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Bahnhofsgleiskarte mit Hervorhebung des Ankunft- und Abfahrtgleises</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Train station platform map, highlighting arrival and departure platforms</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Performmapo de fervoja stacidomo, elstarigante alvenajn kaj forirajn kajojn</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Mapa de andenes de estación de tren, resaltando andenes de llegada y salida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tren-geltokiaren nasaren mapa, iristeko eta irteteko nasak nabarmenduz</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Lähtö- ja saapumislaitureita korostava rautatieasemakartta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La carte des quais de gare, détaillant les quais d'arrivée et de départ.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">מפת רציפי תחנת הרכבת, עם הדגשה על רציפי הגעה ויציאה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Vasútállomás vágánytérképe, kiemelve az érkező és induló peronokat</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Mappa de platteforma de station de traino, evidentiante platteformas de arrivata e partita</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Peta platform stasiun kereta, menyoroti platform kedatangan dan keberangkatan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Mappa dei binari della stazione ferroviaria, evidenziando i binari di arrivo e partenza</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მატარებლის სადგურის პლატფორმების რუკა, ჩამომსვლელი და გასამგზავრებელი პლატფორმების გამოკვეთით</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">출발 및 도착 승강장을 강조한 기차역 승강장 지도</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Perronkaart van treinstation, accentuering van aankomst- en vertrekperrons</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Plan peronu dworca kolejowego, podświetlający perony przybycia i odjazdu</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Mapa das plataformas das estações de comboio que realça as plataformas de partidas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Mapa da plataforma da estação de trem, destacando as plataformas de chegada e partida</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Карта платформ железнодорожной станции с подсветкой платформ прибытия и отправления</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Zemljevid perona železniške postaje s poudarkom na peronih za prihod in odhod</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tågstationskarta för plattformar, som markerar ankomst- och avgångsplattformar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Varış ve kalkış platformlarını vurgulayan tren istasyonu platform haritası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Мапа платформ залізничної станції, підсвічування платформ прибуття та відправлення</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTrain station platform map, highlighting arrival and departure platformsxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">火车站站台地图，高亮显示了入站和出站站台</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">火車站月台地圖，突顯抵達和出發的月台</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-train-station-platform-map.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Train station map showing real-time availability of rental bikes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Mapa de l'estació de tren que mostra la disponibilitat en temps real de les bicicletes de lloguer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Mapa de l'estació de tren que mostra la disponibilitat en temps real de les bicicletes de lloguer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Bahnhofskarte mit Anzeige der Echtzeitverfügbarkeit von Leihfahrrädern</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Train station map showing real-time availability of rental bikes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Mapo de la fervoja stacidomo montrante realtempan haveblecon de lubicikloj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Mapa de estación de tren mostrando la disponibilidad de bicicletas de alquiler en tiempo real</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Tren-geltokiko mapa, alokairuko bizikleten eskuragarritasuna denbora errealean erakusten duena.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Rautatieasemakartta näyttää tosiaikaiset vuokrapolkupyörätiedot</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">La carte de la gare ferroviaire affichant la disponibilité en temps réel des vélos de location.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">מפת תחנות הרכבת מציגה זמינות של אופניים להשכרה בזמן אמת</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Vasútállomás térképe, valós időben megjelenítve a kölcsönözhető kerékpárok elérhetőségét</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Mappa de station de traino monstrante disponibilitate in tempore actual de bicyclettas a locar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Peta stasiun kereta api yang menunjukkan ketersediaan sepeda rental secara real-time.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Mappa della stazione ferroviaria che mostra la disponibilità in tempo reale delle biciclette a noleggio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">რკინიგზის სადგური გასაქირავებელი ველოსიპედების რეალურ დროში ჩვენებით</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">실시간 렌탈 자전거 상황을 표시하는 기차역 지도</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Kaart van treinstation met werkelijk beschikbare huurfietsen</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Plan dworca kolejowego, pokazujący w czasie rzeczywistym dostępność rowerów do wypożyczenia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Mapa das estações de comboios que mostra a disponibilidade em tempo-real das bicicletas de aluguer</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Mapa da estação de trem mostrando a disponibilidade em tempo real de aluguel de bicicletas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Карта железнодорожной станции с показом доступности прокатных велосипедов в режиме реального времени</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Zemljevid železniške postaje sproti prikazuje razpoložljivost koles za najem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Tågstationskarta som visar tillgängliga hyrcyklar i realtid.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kiralık bisikletlerin kullanılabilirliğini gösteren tren istasyonu haritası</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Мапа залізничної станції із показом доступності оренди велосипедів у режимі реального часу</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTrain station map showing real-time availability of rental bikesxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">显示出租自行车实时信息的火车站地图。</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">火車站地圖，顯示租借腳踏車的即時可用狀態</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-train-station-map-with-rental-bike-data.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Detailed information for the select entity on the train station map</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Informació detallada de l'entitat seleccionada en el mapa de l'estació de tren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Informació detallada de l'entitat seleccionada en el mapa de l'estació de tren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Detaillierte Informationen des ausgewählten Elements auf der Bahnhofskarte</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Detailed information for the select entity on the train station map</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Detalaj informoj por la elektita ento sur la mapo de fervoja stacidomo</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Información detallada para la entidad seleccionada en el mapa de la estación de tren</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Hautatutako erakundearen informazio zehatza tren-geltokiko mapan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Yksityiskohtainen tieto rautatieasemakartalta valitusta kohteesta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Informations détaillées pour l'entité sélectionnée sur la carte de la gare.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">מידע מפורט על הישות הנבחרת במפת תחנת הרכבות</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Részletes információk a vasútállomás térképén kiválasztott entitásról</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Information detaliate per le entitate de seliger sur le mappa de station de traino</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Informasi mendetail untuk entitas yang dipilih di peta stasiun kereta</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Informazioni dettagliate per l'entità selezionata sulla mappa della stazione ferroviaria</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">რკინიგზის სადგურზე მონიშნული ელემენტის დეტალური ინფორმაცია</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">기차역 지도에서 선택한 항목의 자세한 정보</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Gedetailleerde informatie voor het te selecteren item op kaart van het treinstation</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Szczegółowe nt. wybranego obiektu na planie dworca kolejowego</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Informações detalhadas para a entidade de selecção no mapa das estações de comboios</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Informação detalhada para a entidade selecionada no mapa da estação de trem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Подробные сведения о выбранном объекте на карте железнодорожной станции</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Podrobne informacije za izbrani predmet na zemljevidu železniške postaje</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Detaljerad information om objektet som valts på tågstationskartan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Tren istasyonu haritasında seçili varlık için ayrıntılı bilgi</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Докладні відомості для позначеного пункту на мапі залізничної станції</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxDetailed information for the select entity on the train station mapxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">火车站地图，显示了所选条目的详细信息</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">在火車站地圖中對於所選項目的詳細資訊</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-train-station-map-details.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <caption>Travel statistics view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Vista de les estadístiques dels viatges</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Vista de les estadístiques dels viatges</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Pohled na statistiky cestování</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Reisestatistikansicht</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Travel statistics view</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eo">Vido de Vojaĝstatistikoj</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Vista de estadísticas de viajes</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Bidai-estatistiken ikuspegia</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Matkan tilastonäkymä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Affichage des statistiques de voyages.</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="he">תצוגת סטטיסטיקת נסיעה</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="hu">Utazási statisztika nézet</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ia">Vista de statistica de viage</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Tampilan statistik perjalanan</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Vista delle statistiche di viaggio</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">მოგზაურობის სტატისტიკის ნახვა</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">여행 통계 보기</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Weergave reisstatistieken</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Widok statystyki podróży</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Área de estatísticas de viagens</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização de estatísticas da viagem</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ru">Просмотр статистики путешествий</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Pogled potovalne statistike</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Visning av resestatistik</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Yolculuk istatistikleri görünümü</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Панель статистики подорожей</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxTravel statistics viewxx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">旅程统计数据视图</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-TW">旅行統計資料檢視</caption>
      <image width="480" height="720" type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/itinerary/kde-itinerary-statistics.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
    <category>Utility</category>
  </categories>
  <url type="homepage">https://community.kde.org/KDE_PIM/KDE_Itinerary</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=KDE+Itinerary</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>itinerary</binary>
  </provides>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.itinerary.desktop</launchable>
  <releases>
    <release version="24.05.0" date="2024-05-23">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for CFR, Eurostar, Indico, IRCTC, Lufthansa, Motel One, SNCB, SNCF, Ticketportal, Trenitalia and VDV eTickets. Added support for public transport data from Serbijavoz and Transitous.</li>
          <li>Show more detailed train coach or vehicle feature information.</li>
          <li>Show per-coach occupancy information when available.</li>
          <li>Allow to manually add ticket barcodes to existing reservations.</li>
          <li>Show DST transition information in the timeline.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.02.2" date="2024-04-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Amsbus.cz, Eurostar, Finnair, Moongate, UK national railway and VR.</li>
          <li>Fix displaying public transport departure disruptions.</li>
          <li>Fix Apple Wallet pass rendering issues.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.02.1" date="2024-03-21">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Deutsche Bahn, Eckerö Line, European Sleeper, Eventim, Flibco, Leo Express, National Express, ÖBB, osmcal.org, Salzbergwerk, SNCF and ti.to.</li>
          <li>Filter implausible geo coder results on address editing.</li>
          <li>Fix overlap between floating map button and arrival details on the journey details page.</li>
          <li>Improve Deutsche Bahn realtime information when facing cancelled or replacement trains.</li>
          <li>Improve train coach type detection in the coach layout view.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="24.02.0" date="2024-02-28">
      <url>https://kde.org/announcements/megarelease/6/#itinerary</url>
      <description>
        <p>We improved the usability of Itinerary on phones by making common actions available on a bottom navigation bar which makes it easy to switch to your passes and your current trip.</p>
        <p>The main timeline was redesigned and now entries can be expanded inline to show the intermediate stops and ongoing delays and disruptions. Speaking of events, it is now possible to manually add and edit entries and to share entire trips or single reservations to your phone via KDE Connect.</p>
        <p>The indoor map in Itinerary now lists all amenities in the building or area you are currently looking at. This helps with things like finding a place to grab a coffee in a big train station, or searching for a place to get food in the vicinity of your hotel. This feature is powered by OpenStreetMap, works without the need to connect to the internet and no search terms ever leave your device.</p>
        <p>When viewing a trip details, in addition to being able to consult the list of stops, it can look at a map of the trip.</p>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.5" date="2024-02-15"/>
    <release version="23.08.4" date="2023-12-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for 12go, Eurostar, Flixbus, Motel One, SAS and Thalys.</li>
          <li>Improved support for European FCB railway ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li>Support for Eurostar onboard API.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.3" date="2023-11-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix handling of canceled intermediate stops on board of DB ICEs.</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for booking.com, DB, European Sleeper, Iberia, PKP, Pretix, Qatar Airways.</li>
          <li>Fix parsing certain invalid Apple Wallet message catalogs.</li>
          <li>Remove unnecessary PDF fonts to reduce the APK size.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.2" date="2023-10-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow to enable notifications on Android 13.</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aegean, Amadeus, bookingkit, GWR, Pretix, Renfe, ÖBB and UK railway tickets.</li>
          <li>Render more amenity details on the train station map.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.1" date="2023-09-14">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aer Lingus, Amtrak, British Airways, Deutsche Bahn, GVH, premiumkino, Slovak Lines and ZSSK.</li>
          <li>Fix editing bus and train elements without an associated ticket.</li>
          <li>Fix unnecessarily broad permissions on Android.</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet generic pass thumbnail images.</li>
          <li>Fix progress display on the initial journey stopover in the live status view.</li>
          <li>Display luggage lockers, lost &amp; found offices and ariport baggage claim belts on the indoor map.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.08.0" date="2023-08-24">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Preferred transport modes can now selected for all public transport searches.</li>
          <li>Public transport line logos are now also available for some regional and long distance rail services.</li>
          <li>Added support for railway coach layouts for more types of trains.</li>
          <li>Added support for importing Deutsche Bahn and SNCF online tickets.</li>
          <li>Added location sharing via Matrix.</li>
          <li>Consider coach layout and seat reservation data to highlight the departure/arrival spot on a platform.</li>
          <li>New look for the timeline entries and the editing pages.</li>
          <li>New or improved onboard API support for Aegean Air, Deutsche Bahn and ÖBB.</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aegean Air, Aer Lingus, Air Asia, Air France, Atlatos, Bäder Suite, BlaBlaCar, bookingkit, CD, Cinemaxx, Cooltix, DSB, Eventbrite, FerriesInGreece, Grimaldi Lines, Iberia, KLM, Koleje Malopolskie, KTEL Thesprotias, Lufthansa, Ouigo Spain, PKP, UK railways, SAS, SBB, Slovak Lines, SNCB, spiritec, Spring Airlines, Sunny Cars, Thalys, Trenitalia, York Kino and ZSSK.</li>
          <li>Added support for importing ActivityPub events.</li>
          <li>Added support for editing many more reservation and ticket details.</li>
          <li>Documents can now be attached to all tickets and reservations, and are automatically attached in more cases.</li>
          <li>New hotel, event and restaurant reservation can be created by adding a URL to their schema.org annotated website.</li>
          <li>Added support for extracting travel data in Apple iCal events.</li>
          <li>Improved notifications in case of Apple Wallet pass updates.</li>
          <li>Improved display of ticket validity times in the passes and programs view.</li>
          <li>Improved display of public transport cancellations and long disruption notes.</li>
          <li>Fixed searching for international railway connections sometimes not finding any result.</li>
          <li>Fixed weather icons sometimes wrongly using the night variants during the day.</li>
          <li>Fixed too rapid realtime data update queries in case of network errors.</li>
          <li>Fixed exported events not being editable by other calendaring apps on Android.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.3" date="2023-07-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Color Line, DJH, Fjord Line, Flixbus, Grimladi Lines, onepagebooking, SNCB, Thalys and Trenitalia.</li>
          <li>Fixed a crash on Android when importing a file with a space in its path.</li>
          <li>Fixed public transport queries for VRS.</li>
          <li>Fixed missing transport mode information for some OpenTripPlanner results.</li>
          <li>Filter implausible walking paths from public transport routers.</li>
          <li>Fixed importing boat or ferry reservations from the calendar.</li>
          <li>Fixed an infinite loop when computing indoor map arguments.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.2" date="2023-06-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fixed automatic transfer selection producing nonsense when geo coordinates are missing.</li>
          <li>Fixed showing of attached Appled Wallet passes for trains, hotels, busses and car rental reservations.</li>
          <li>Fixed a potential deadlock on updating currency conversion rates.</li>
          <li>Fixed attaching documents to multi-traveler reservations.</li>
          <li>Improved scrolling speed of the timeline view.</li>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for European Sleeper, IndiGo, PKP, Qatar Airways, SBB, SNCB, Thalys as well as for Latvian and Lithuanian railway tickets.</li>
          <li>New generic ERA FCB ticket barcode extractor.</li>
          <li>Improved extractor for restaurant data in websites.</li>
          <li>Fixed merging of public transport disruption notes from different sources.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.1" date="2023-05-11">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved travel document extractors for Air Asia, ATPI, B&amp;B Hotels, Best Western, CD, FlixBus, Gepard Express, Grimaldi Lines, MAV, SNCB and Vueling.</li>
          <li>Support importing various variants of the Deutschlandticket.</li>
          <li>Fixed rendering of MAV ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li>Fixed public transport queries in the Czech Republic and the UK.</li>
          <li>Fixed imported PDFs losing their file name on Android.</li>
          <li>Improved Apple Wallet boarding pass layout for overflowing labels.</li>
          <li>Improved handling of canceled elements in the timeline.</li>
          <li>Improved rendering of barrier elements in the train station map.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="23.04.0" date="2023-04-20">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New or improved travel document extractors for Aegean Air, Amadeus, availpro, BlaBlaCar, Deutsche Bahn, Kinoheld, Meetup, National Express, ÖBB, Octorate, Ouigo, Premier Inn, SNCF, Taiwan Highspeed Rail and whyline.</li>
          <li>Support for Eurostar, SBB and UK railway ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li>New live status page using onboard vehicle API.</li>
          <li>New UI for reservation details pages.</li>
          <li>Faster loading of train station and airport maps.</li>
          <li>Improved display of doors, trees, barrier blocks, platform section markers and accessibility information on train station maps.</li>
          <li>Allow to enable LED light for barcode scanning.</li>
          <li>Fix wrong public transport service being used in France.</li>
          <li>Fix public transport data access in Switzerland.</li>
          <li>Fix handling of pasted URLs.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.3" date="2023-03-02">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved data extraction for Flixbus and UK railway tickets.</li>
          <li>Fixed eliding of stop names in the journey view.</li>
          <li>Fixed missing timezone display for times in UTC.</li>
          <li>Fixed train station map stacking order for layered building parts.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.2" date="2023-02-02">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved data extraction for booking.com, Deutsche Bahn, Indico, MÁV, onepagebooking and Pretix.</li>
          <li>Improved merging of separate train ticket and seat reservation data.</li>
          <li>Fixed rendering of certain Apple Wallet event tickets.</li>
          <li>Fixed importing multiple generic Apple Wallet passes.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.1" date="2023-01-05">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support importing of Mobilizon events.</li>
          <li>Improved travel data extraction for Eventim, MÁV, NH Hotels, Trenitalia.</li>
          <li>Fix display of floating rental vehicles.</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet event passes with background images.</li>
          <li>Improve map gesture interaction on favorite location picker.</li>
          <li>Fix interaction with near-horizontal or near-vertical stairs on the train station map.</li>
          <li>Fix handling of always closed opening hours.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.12.0" date="2022-12-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for boat/ferry reservations.</li>
          <li>Support for ICAO VDS vaccination certificates.</li>
          <li>Improved floor level switching for staircases in station/airport maps.</li>
          <li>Stacking order and hit detection fixes for the station/airport maps.</li>
          <li>Fix driving side informations for people living in left-driving countries.</li>
          <li>Fix date/time input for manual train/bus journey searches.</li>
          <li>Fix Railjet trains having no coach layout inside Germany.</li>
          <li>Support for ERA FCB ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li>Various travel document extractor additions and improvements.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.3" date="2022-11-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New travel data extractor for Italo train tickets.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.2" date="2022-10-13">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved travel data extraction for Airbnb, Amadeus, BlaBlaCar, Eventim, Ryanair, SNCF, Thalys, Vueling.</li>
          <li>Handle transliteration when comparing traveler names.</li>
          <li>Fix trip grouping when connecting journey is part of a different reservation.</li>
          <li>Fix selecting the right Apple Wallet event ticket for multi-attendee events.</li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet event tickets.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.1" date="2022-09-08">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improve size and positioning of map overlays.</li>
          <li>Improved travel data extractors for Amtrak, Flixbus and Vistara.</li>
          <li>Improved airport terminal and gate detection.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.08.0" date="2022-08-18">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved calendar import, allowing more fine-grained selection and supporting Linux too.</li>
          <li>Support for exporting reservations to the calendar.</li>
          <li>Support for passes and program cards that aren't tied to a specific trip, such as flat-rate or time interval tickets or discount program memberships.</li>
          <li>Support for adding train and bus trips from online journey searches.</li>
          <li>Integrated barcode scanner.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.3" date="2022-07-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix monorail platforms being misdetected as regular railway.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.2" date="2022-06-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Improved travel data extraction for Thalys, UK national rail, Eurowings and Eventbrite.</li>
          <li>Fixed train load information parsing for German public transport operators.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.1" date="2022-05-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix the wrong country being displayed in formatted addresses.</li>
          <li>Display all supported barcode types in Apple Wallet passes.</li>
          <li>Improved travel document extractors for booking.com, Eurowings, onepagebooking.com and SNCF.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="22.04.0" date="2022-04-21">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Support for overnight train coaches in the train coach layout view.</li>
          <li>Show currencies and optionally current conversion rates when entering a different country.</li>
          <li>Allow to add train trips from an online journey query to the timeline.</li>
          <li>New or improved extractors for Renfe, SNCF, ÖBB, Spring Airlines, Peach Aviation.</li>
          <li>Highlight severe weather conditions in the weather forecast.</li>
          <li>Show public holidays in the timeline.</li>
          <li>Fixed high DPI scaling issues in the train coach view.</li>
          <li>Support for Amtrak and IATA train station identifiers.</li>
          <li>Support for importing Danish COVID certificates.</li>
          <li>Follow system settings on Linux for which external map application to use.</li>
          <li>Add jump list action to directly open the current ticket.</li>
          <li>Fixed geometry reassembly issues in the train station map.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.3" date="2022-03-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add travel data extraction from Air France ticket PDF documents.</li>
          <li>Fix locale-aware formatting of numbers.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.2" date="2022-02-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix trip grouping producing wrong results in densely populated areas.</li>
          <li>Improve vector barcode detection in PDF documents.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.1" date="2022-01-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix station map positioning for elements without live data.</li>
          <li>Improved travel document extraction for Amtrak and VIA Rail.</li>
          <li>Support for alternative Hafas platform formats.</li>
          <li>Improved opening hours evaluation in the station maps.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.12.0" date="2021-12-09">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>New health certificate user interface.</li>
          <li>New navigation maneuver details page for individual transport or walking journey sections.</li>
          <li>Smarter transfer auto-selection.</li>
          <li>Live disruption information and journey details for bus trips.</li>
          <li>Ability to shorten train and bus trips.</li>
          <li>Additional individual transport modes for transfers.</li>
          <li>Improved platform identification for trams and subways.</li>
          <li>Easier accessible barcode scan mode, and support for PDF417 ticket barcodes.</li>
          <li>Improved data import feedback.</li>
          <li>Fixed pinch zoom on station maps.</li>
          <li>Improved Apple Wallet pass rendering.</li>
          <li>Warn about rental vehicles with limited remaining range.</li>
          <li>Numerous improvements to travel document data extraction.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.3" date="2021-11-04">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix icon size issues on high DPI screens.</li>
          <li>Fix map panning leaving the favorite location selector page.</li>
          <li>Fix determining departure country for location changes.</li>
          <li>Fix erroneous merging of train trips with the same line on the same day.</li>
          <li>Fix parsing of OTP rental vehicle information.</li>
          <li>Apply timezone information correctly to flight reservations with incomplete time information.</li>
          <li>Improved data extraction for various providers.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.2" date="2021-10-07">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Add support for SMART Health Card (SHC) vaccination certificates.</li>
          <li>Don't trigger the connection warning when there is no previous arrival time.</li>
          <li>Show correct number of attached documents for multi-traveller trips.</li>
          <li>Show escalators to/from intermediate floor levels correctly in the indoor map. </li>
          <li>Fix rendering of Apple Wallet pass rich-text back fields.</li>
          <li>Improved data extraction for SNCF, Accor, Feratel and onepagebooking.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.1" date="2021-09-02">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Properly import mail attachments shared from FairEmail.</li>
          <li>Improvements for importing data from Airdo, MÁV, Regionado, Ryanair and SNCF.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="21.08.0" date="2021-08-12">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Health certificate manager for DIVOC and EU DGC vaccination, test and recovery certificates.</li>
          <li>GPX import and export of favorite locations and GPX export of trips for Nextcloud Maps interoperability.</li>
          <li>Support for local German public transport operators INVG, RSAG, VRT and VSN.</li>
          <li>Improved travel document extractor.</li>
          <li>Various fixes to the page flow.</li>
          <li>Entire trip groups can now be deleted.</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
  </releases>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::f_droid">https://community.kde.org/Android/FDroid#KDE_F-Droid_Release_Repository</value>
    <value key="KDE::google_play">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.kde.itinerary</value>
    <value key="KDE::matrix">#itinerary:kde.org</value>
  </custom>
</component>
